- [Haemi] Go in, go in - [Yoojeong] Uh
- [هايمي] ادخل، ادخل - [يوجيونج] اه
[Rhythmic music plays]
[تشغيل الموسيقى الإيقاعية]
[Sound of car door closing]
[صوت إغلاق باب السيارة]
[Oncoming car driving sound]
[صوت قيادة السيارة القادمة]
I'm going too
سأذهب أيضًا
[Sound of car door opening]
[صوت فتح باب السيارة]
[Sound of car door closing]
[صوت إغلاق باب السيارة]
[Secret Music]
{\an8[الموسيقى السرية]
- Me, knight - [Taxi Driver] Yes
- أنا أيها الفارس - [سائق التاكسي] نعم
- Could you please stop in front of me?
- هل يمكنك التوقف أمامي من فضلك؟
[sigh]
[تنهد]
[cell phone vibrates]
[يهتز الهاتف الخليوي]
[Sound of a mobile phone being picked up]
[صوت هاتف محمول يتم التقاطه]
[Schematic] Come quickly you should party with me
[تخطيطي] تعال بسرعة يجب أن تحتفل معي
- crazy bastard - [Uneasy music]
- وغد مجنون - [موسيقى مضطربة]
[Cell phone end sound]
[صوت نهاية الهاتف الخليوي]
[Jay] I heard Yujeong is pregnant. I couldn't bear to say it
[جاي] سمعت أن Yujeong حامل. لم أستطع تحمل أن أقول ذلك
Still, I don't think this is it
ومع ذلك، لا أعتقد أن هذا هو الحال
Where are you? talk to me
أين أنت؟ تحدث معي
[Text sending sound]
[صوت إرسال النص]
[sigh]
[تنهد]
Did you go to the hotel by any chance?
هل ذهبت إلى الفندق بالصدفة؟
[Text sending sound]
[صوت إرسال النص]
[Call connection tone]
[نغمة اتصال المكالمة]
[Voice guidance] Can't connect After the beep sound, go to Sorisam…
[التوجيه الصوتي] لا يمكن الاتصال بعد سماع صوت الصافرة، انتقل إلى Sorisam...
[Soaring music]
[موسيقى صاخبة]
Me, driver
أنا، السائق
I'm sorry Could you please go back to the hotel?
أنا آسف هل يمكنك العودة إلى الفندق من فضلك؟
[Doorbell sounds]
[أصوات جرس الباب]
[panicked breathing]
[التنفس المذعور]
Are you here?
هل أنت هنا؟
[nervous music]
[موسيقى عصبية]
[Dosik’s footsteps]
[خطى دوسيك]
[Scheme] Let’s have a drink
[مخطط] دعونا نتناول مشروبًا
Looking at your expression I think it's serious
النظر في التعبير الخاص بك أعتقد أن الأمر خطير
- [Sound of pouring alcohol] - [Sound of clattering glasses]
- [صوت صب الكحول] - [صوت قعقعة النظارات]
That
ذلك
I saw it
رأيت ذلك
A text message sent by Dosik to Yuna
رسالة نصية أرسلها دوسيك إلى يونا
[Laughs] No, that girl. Without even being careful
[يضحك] لا، تلك الفتاة. دون حتى أن نكون حذرين
Mr. Dosik
السيد دوسيك
Now in two weeks I'm marrying Yujeong.
الآن خلال اسبوعين سأتزوج يوجيونغ.
You can just get married, what's the problem?
يمكنك الزواج فقط، ما هي المشكلة؟
[Excited breathing]
[التنفس متحمس]
Stop contacting Yuna.
توقف عن التواصل مع يونا.
Otherwise, to Yoojung. I'll tell you everything
وإلا إلى يوجونغ. سأخبرك بكل شيء
Mr. Do-sik, even doing drugs.
السيد دو سيك، حتى أنه يتعاطى المخدرات.
Ha, me, Yoo Yoo-na, that bitch really
ها، أنا، يو يو نا، تلك العاهرة حقًا
[Schematic] Is there any secret to losing?
[رسم تخطيطي] هل هناك سر للخسارة؟
No, should I try it too? Go Yoona's Secret
لا، هل يجب أن أحاول ذلك أيضاً؟ اذهب إلى سر يونا
Unique or secret?
فريدة أم سرية؟
- [Schematic] Yuna said to you - [Meaningful music]
- [تخطيطي] قالت لك يونا - [موسيقى ذات معنى]
You said you were a fashion designer, right?
قلت أنك كنت مصمم أزياء، أليس كذلك؟
Actually, she is the master of the room salon.
في الواقع، هي سيدة صالون الغرفة.
[Sharp sound effect]
[تأثير صوت حاد]
It's also very famous in Gangnam
كما أنها مشهورة جدًا في جانجنام
[Excited breathing]
[التنفس متحمس]
This doesn't make sense
هذا لا معنى له
[Scheme] That kind of bar madam Why did I approach you guys?
[مخطط] هذا النوع من الحانة سيدتي لماذا اقتربت منكم يا رفاق؟
Sometimes customers Because I want a good family like you.
في بعض الأحيان العملاء لأنني أريد عائلة جيدة مثلك.
The kids at the bar are boring
الأطفال في البار مملون
You guys trick the customers into telling me I did it to sell it.
أنتم يا رفاق تخدعون العملاء لإخباري لقد فعلت ذلك لبيعه.
Hey
مهلا
-Are you weak again? - [Ice rattling sound]
-هل أنت ضعيف مرة أخرى؟ - [صوت قعقعة الجليد]
Oh, if you don't believe me think about it, think about it
أوه، إذا كنت لا تصدقني فكر في الأمر، فكر في الأمر
How did Yujeong and I become connected?
كيف أصبحنا أنا وYujeong متصلين؟
[light sigh]
[تنهد خفيف]
- [Yuna’s laughter] - [Yujeong] Oh, really
- [ضحكة يونا] - [يوجيونغ] أوه، حقًا
Just don't laugh
فقط لا تضحك
[Yuna] By the way, Yoojeong
[يونا] بالمناسبة، يوجيونغ
I have a really nice older brother. Would you like to meet sometime?
لدي أخ أكبر لطيف حقًا. هل ترغب في أن نلتقي في وقت ما؟
[shocked breathing]
[التنفس بالصدمة]
A very nice oppa why would you meet me
اوبا جميل جدا لماذا تقابلني
No, that guy is really nice.
لا، هذا الرجل لطيف حقا.
[Yuna] Let’s meet once, okay?
[يونا] دعونا نلتقي مرة واحدة، حسنا؟
Do you know that Hae-mi is a drug addict?
هل تعلم أن هاي مي مدمنة مخدرات؟
[Schematic] That too That’s how Yuna did it.
[التخطيطي] هذا أيضا هكذا فعلت يونا ذلك.
[Haemi's tired breathing]
[تنفس هيمي المتعب]
[Haemi] Our hotel’s spring event To set up
[هايمي] حدث الربيع في فندقنا لاقامة
Moving forward without moving The 3rd and 4th are nights, so it's a big deal.
المضي قدما دون التحرك الليلة الثالثة والرابعة هي ليالٍ، لذا فهي مشكلة كبيرة.
Is there any medicine that prevents you from falling asleep?
هل هناك دواء يمنعك من النوم؟
[Yuna] Would you like to try this? They say it’s a fatigue remedy.
[يونا] هل ترغب في تجربة هذا؟ يقولون أنه علاج التعب.
[Haemi] Really?
[هيمي] حقا؟
lie
كذبة
[sigh]
[تنهد]
to me now Are you lying?
لي الآن هل تكذب؟
[Scheme] No, if you don’t believe me Or check with Yuna directly.
[مخطط] لا، إذا كنت لا تصدقني أو تحقق مع يونا مباشرة.
'Cause I really don't care
لأنني حقا لا أهتم
[Jay's surprised gasp]
[شهقة جاي المتفاجئة]
[Heavy breathing] I
[التنفس الثقيل] أنا
A guy like you is with Yoojung Do you think I'll let you get married?
رجل مثلك مع Yoojung هل تعتقد أنني سأسمح لك بالزواج؟
Yoo-jeong ruins the wedding.
ويفسد "يو جيونغ" حفل الزفاف.
I'm going to report you, on drug charges
سأقوم بالإبلاغ عنك بتهم المخدرات
If this marriage breaks up
إذا انفصل هذا الزواج
Who loses more?
من يخسر أكثر؟
[Music that heightens tension]
[الموسيقى التي تزيد من التوتر]
Yujeong is not even single.
Yujeong ليس حتى أعزبًا.
[Scheme] You can report me for drugs
[مخطط] يمكنك الإبلاغ عني بسبب المخدرات
I hate the police All you have to do is blow it up
أنا أكره الشرطة كل ما عليك فعله هو تفجيره
[Do-shik laughs] Are you going crazy?
[يضحك دو شيك] هل ستصاب بالجنون؟
Because I can’t do this or that, huh?
لأنني لا أستطيع أن أفعل هذا أو ذاك، هاه؟
[Dosik’s sneer]
[سخرية دوسيك]
[shaking breathing]
[اهتزاز التنفس]
[Sound of a glass being put down]
[صوت وضع كأس]
[Sound of gulping]
[صوت البلع]
- [Heavy breathing] - [Sharp sound effect]
- [التنفس الثقيل] - [تأثير صوت حاد]
[dark music]
[الموسيقى المظلمة]
[rattling sound]
[صوت قعقعة]
[Dosik’s voice rings] You Crazy...
[يرن صوت دوسيك] أنت مجنون...
Did you drink that drink?
هل شربت ذلك المشروب؟
[Dosik’s evil laughter]
[ضحكة دوسيك الشريرة]
[rattling sound]
[صوت قعقعة]
[Birdsong]
[أغنية العصافير]
[Sound of shoes again and again]
[صوت الأحذية مرارا وتكرارا]
[Rough breathing]
[التنفس الخشن]
[cell phone vibrates]
[يهتز الهاتف الخليوي]
[Yuna] How do you like my gift?
[يونا] كيف تحب هديتي؟
[sigh]
[تنهد]
[Jay] Don’t do anything useless
[جاي] لا تفعل أي شيء عديم الفائدة
- [Footsteps ringing] - [Meaningful music]
- [رنين خطى] - [موسيقى ذات معنى]
[eerie sound effect]
[مؤثرات صوتية غريبة]
[Sound of approaching footsteps]
[صوت خطوات تقترب]
[Tense sound effect]
[مؤثرات صوتية متوترة]
[Music that heightens tension]
[الموسيقى التي تزيد من التوتر]
[Footsteps sound]
[صوت خطى]
[Heavy sound effect]
[مؤثرات صوتية ثقيلة]
[Jay's surprised voice]
[صوت جاي المتفاجئ]
[Footsteps continue to ring]
[تستمر الخطى في الرنين]
[Music stops]
[تتوقف الموسيقى]
[Child] Why are you doing this, Aunt?
[الطفل] لماذا تفعل هذا، العمة؟
[eerie sound effect]
[مؤثرات صوتية غريبة]
[shaking breathing]
[اهتزاز التنفس]
[Exhales harshly]
[يزفر بقوة]
[Meaningful music]
[موسيقى ذات معنى]
[surprised gasp]
[شهقة متفاجئة]
[Sound of footsteps tapping]
[صوت وقع خطوات]
you
أنت
Where did you get this mask?
من أين حصلت على هذا القناع؟
The director gave it to me.
لقد أعطاها لي المدير.
[eerie music]
[موسيقى غريبة]
[Sound of a child running]
[صوت طفل يركض]
[light sigh]
[تنهد خفيف]
[sniffling sound]
[صوت الاستنشاق]
[Director’s voice]
[صوت المخرج]
[Sharp sound effect]
[تأثير صوت حاد]
[surprised gasp]
[شهقة متفاجئة]
[Sound of children talking]
[صوت أطفال يتحدثون]
[Director] No, not you, not you...
[المدير] لا، ليس أنت، ليس أنت...
Jumper, put it here in the jumper.
أيها الطائر، ضعه هنا في الطائر.
- Huh? - [Children talking]
- هاه؟ - [الأطفال يتحدثون]
- Hello - [Child’s speaking voice]
- مرحبا - [صوت الطفل الناطق]
- [Director] Uh, hello. -Where did this mask come from?
- [المدير] اه، مرحبا. -من أين جاء هذا القناع؟
[Laughing] Ah, this town The stationery store owner
[يضحك] آه، هذه المدينة صاحب محل القرطاسية
I gave it to the kids to play with.
أعطيتها للأطفال ليلعبوا بها.
[Jay] Where is the stationery?
[جاي] أين القرطاسية؟
Uh, Atom stationery company.
اه، شركة اتوم للقرطاسية.
Hey, in front of our orphanage It’s been a while since you’ve been in business.
مهلا، أمام دار الأيتام لدينا لقد مر وقت طويل منذ أن كنت في العمل.
[Jay] Ah, yes
[جاي] آه، نعم
[Director] Junhee Don't lie down on the floor
[المخرج] جونهي لا تستلقي على الأرض
- Teacher, Junhee is lying down again. - [Sound of putting down mask]
- المعلم، Junhee يستلقي مرة أخرى. - [صوت وضع القناع]
[Sound of urgent footsteps moving away]
[صوت خطى عاجلة تبتعد]
[sigh]
[تنهد]
[shaking breathing]
[اهتزاز التنفس]
[Rough breathing]
[التنفس الخشن]
- [Haemi] Jay! - [Sound of approaching footsteps]
- [هيمي] جاي! - [صوت خطى تقترب]
You found it
لقد وجدت ذلك
[Yoojeong] What’s wrong with your complexion?
[يوجيونغ] ما هو الخطأ في بشرتك؟
- What is that? - [Jay] Ah
- ما هذا؟ - [جاي] آه
- Oh, this is nothing. - [Sound of putting down mask]
- أوه، هذا لا شيء. - [صوت وضع القناع]
[Grass bug crying]
[بكاء حشرة العشب]
[Haemi] That bastard Ki Yun-cheol Why did you come here?
[هايمي] ذلك الوغد كي يون تشيول لماذا أتيت إلى هنا؟
make people uncomfortable
تجعل الناس غير مرتاحين
[Leo] With that person Did something bad happen?
[ليو] مع هذا الشخص هل حدث شيء سيء؟
Earlier, Yujeong's sister also When I saw that person, my expression got worse.
وفي وقت سابق، أخت Yujeong أيضا عندما رأيت ذلك الشخص، أصبح تعبيري أسوأ.
[Haemi] No, the main character is Jae-yi.
[هايمي] لا، الشخصية الرئيسية هي جاي يي.
For no reason I came here Because I'm in the spotlight
بدون سبب جئت إلى هنا لأنني في دائرة الضوء
[Yoojeong] Oh, Jae-ya
[يوجيونج] أوه، جاي يا
[Yujeong’s laughter]
[ضحكة يوجيونغ]
Is this your first time seeing me?
هل هذه هي المرة الأولى التي تراني فيها؟
My fiance, Song Je-hyuk
خطيبي سونغ جي هيوك
Nice to meet you, my name is Dojae.
سعدت بلقائك، اسمي دوجاي.
Hello, this is Song Jehyuk.
مرحبًا، هذا سونغ جيهيوك.
Strangely enough, I It doesn't feel like I'm seeing you for the first time
ومن الغريب أنني لا أشعر وكأنني أراك للمرة الأولى
To Mr. Yujeong But I've heard so much about it
إلى السيد يوجيونج لكني سمعت الكثير عن ذلك
[Haemi laughs] That’s Jae-yi. It's because it appears on TV so often.
[يضحك هيمي] هذا جاي يي. هذا لأنه يظهر على شاشة التلفزيون في كثير من الأحيان.
I saw a celebrity at the hotel the other day
لقد رأيت أحد المشاهير في الفندق في ذلك اليوم
'Huh? hey!' And
"هاه؟" يا!' و
- You hit me on the back. - [Leo’s laughter]
- لقد ضربتني على الظهر. - [ضحكة ليو]
I thought he was my younger brother [laughter]
اعتقدت أنه أخي الأصغر [ضحك]
[Leo] I
[ليو] أنا
- Now, now, now, let’s not be like this. - [Haemi’s laughter]
- الآن، الآن، الآن، دعونا لا نكون هكذا. - [ضحك هيمي]
Let’s all go have a drink together.
دعونا جميعا نذهب لتناول مشروب معا.
My older sister, Jay, is running for office. Let's celebrate too
أختي الكبرى، جاي، تترشح لمنصب. دعونا نحتفل أيضا
- [Leo] Let’s go. - Oh, there
- [ليو] دعنا نذهب. - أوه، هناك
[Jay] Today I I'm not feeling well, so...
[جاي] اليوم أنا أنا لا أشعر أنني بحالة جيدة، لذلك...
Hey, we got together because of you, is that why?
مهلا، لقد اجتمعنا معا بسببك، هل هذا هو السبب؟
[Haemi] Go, go and relieve yourself.
[هايمي] اذهب، اذهب وخفف عن نفسك.
Are you okay too?
هل أنت بخير أيضا؟
Uh, can we...
اه هل يمكننا...
[Jehyuk] Let’s go
[جيهيوك] دعنا نذهب
You can't miss out on Jay's congratulations.
لا يمكنك تفويت تهنئة جاي.
[Haemi] Okay, let’s go
[هايمي] حسنًا، لنذهب
I'm having a drink on a day like this
أنا أتناول مشروبًا في يوم مثل هذا
[Leo] Let’s go
[ليو] دعنا نذهب
- [Haemi] Come quickly! - [Yoojeong] Uh
- [هيمي] تعال بسرعة! - [يوجيونج] اه
[Haemi and Leo’s footsteps moving away]
[خطوات هيمي وليو تبتعد]
What's going on?
ماذا يحدث؟
You don’t like drinking places with a lot of people.
أنت لا تحب أماكن الشرب مع الكثير من الناس.
Still, I have to go
ومع ذلك، لا بد لي من الذهاب
These are Yujeong’s friends.
هؤلاء هم أصدقاء Yujeong.
[breath mixed with laughter]
[نفس ممزوج بالضحك]
- [Interesting Music] - [Leo] Ta-da
- [موسيقى مثيرة للاهتمام] - [ليو] تا دا
[Elasticity]
[مرونة]
- [Haemi’s laughter] - [Leo] Now
- [ضحك هيمي] - [ليو] الآن
[Yujeong’s laughter]
[ضحكة يوجيونغ]
Jay's older sister
الأخت الكبرى لجاي
Brother
أخي
Ah, sister
اه يا أخت
- [Yujeong’s breathing mixed with laughter] - Now
- [تنفس يوجيونج ممزوج بالضحك] - الآن
[Haemi] Fish oil
[هيمي] زيت السمك
- [Sound of strong breathing] - [Haemi’s laughter]
- [صوت تنفس قوي] - [ضحك هيمي]
- Hey, please wake up. - [Ice rattling sound]
- مهلا، يرجى الاستيقاظ. - [صوت قعقعة الجليد]
- [Haemi] Okay, okay, let’s wake up. - [Leo] Wake up, sister.
- [هيمي] حسنًا، حسنًا، فلنستيقظ. - [ليو] استيقظي يا أختي.
[Leo] Okay then
[ليو] حسنًا إذن
For sister Jae-i’s election!
لانتخاب الأخت جاي آي!
[Haemi, Leo] For!
[هيمي، ليو] ل!
[Together] For!
[معا] ل!
- [Haemi and Leo cheer] -Thank you
- [هيمي وليو يهتفان] -شكرا لك
[ice clattering sound]
[صوت قعقعة الجليد]
[Sound of swallowing]
[صوت البلع]
[Leo and Haemi’s cool elasticity]
[مرونة ليو وهيمي الرائعة]
[Leo’s cool breathing]
[تنفس ليو البارد]
[Leo] Huh?
[ليو] هاه؟
Hey, sister, the first drink is one shot.
يا أختي، أول مشروب هو جرعة واحدة.
I'm sorry I don't think it will go over well
أنا آسف لا أعتقد أن الأمر سيسير على ما يرام
[Leo] I’ll definitely skip this one. Why?
[ليو] سأتخطى هذا بالتأكيد. لماذا؟
This, a certain golden ratio in Cheongdam-dong Because it is a liquor made
هذه نسبة ذهبية معينة في تشيونغدام دونغ لأنه خمور مصنوعة
Yes, try it.
نعم، جربه.
[Hae-mi's breathing sounds mixed with laughter]
[أصوات تنفس هاي مي ممزوجة بالضحك]
[Yoojeong] Mr. Leo
[يوجيونغ] السيد ليو
Our Jay is Don't offer too much alcohol
جاي لدينا هو لا تقدم الكثير من الكحول
Jae-yi, a drink poured by a man I never drink it
جاي يي، مشروب يصبه رجل أنا لا أشربه أبدا
- [shocked breathing] - [Leo] Oh, why?
- [التنفس بالصدمة] - [ليو] أوه، لماذا؟
Long time ago, some guy Spit on alcohol?
منذ وقت طويل، بعض الرجل يبصقون على الكحول؟
[Laughing] Oh my!
[يضحك] يا إلهي!
[Haemi, Yujeong’s throat cough]
[هايمي، سعال الحلق لدى يوجيونغ]
[Leo's breathing sounds mixed with laughter]
[أصوات تنفس ليو ممزوجة بالضحك]
[dark music]
[الموسيقى المظلمة]
[Jay's exasperated breathing]
[تنفس جاي الغاضب]
[eerie sound effect]
[مؤثرات صوتية غريبة]
- [Jay’s surprised gasp] - [Intense sound effect]
- [شهقة جاي المتفاجئة] - [تأثير صوتي مكثف]
[Leo is frustrated] Ah, sister.
[ليو محبط] آه، أختي.
Oh, just the alcohol we give you Let’s have a drink, Solka.
أوه، فقط الكحول الذي نقدمه لك دعنا نتناول مشروبًا، سولكا.
Here to sister Jay Where is the man?
هنا للأخت جاي أين الرجل؟
I'm our Haemi older sister Jehyuk's older brother is Yujeong's older sister.
أنا أختنا الكبرى هيمي الأخ الأكبر لجيهيوك هو أخت يوجيونغ الكبرى.
[Jehyuk’s light smile]
[ابتسامة جيهيوك الخفيفة]
But...
لكن...
Then, let’s have some alcohol.
ثم دعونا نتناول بعض الكحول.
[Jehyuk] Why?
[جيهيوك] لماذا؟
[Laughing] Do I look like a man, do I?
[يضحك] هل أبدو كرجل، أليس كذلك؟
[Jehyuk’s light smile]
[ابتسامة جيهيوك الخفيفة]
[panicked breathing]
[التنفس المذعور]
[Sound of picking up a glass]
[صوت التقاط الزجاج]
I'll have a drink, alcohol
سآخذ مشروبًا، كحولًا
[Sound of approaching footsteps]
[صوت خطوات تقترب]
[ice clattering sound]
[صوت قعقعة الجليد]
[Kanghu] Please stop. To people who don't like it
[كانغو] من فضلك توقف. للأشخاص الذين لا يحبون ذلك
[Leo] Ah, bro
[ليو] آه، وإخوانه
I think Jae-ni was nervous. I'm asking you to let me off the hook.
أعتقد أن جاي ني كان متوترًا. أنا أطلب منك أن تسمح لي بالخروج من الخطاف.
Well…
حسنا...
Don't do that, come quickly too. Let's have a drink
لا تفعل ذلك، تعال سريعًا أيضًا. دعونا نتناول مشروبًا
[Jehyuk] If anyone sees
[جيهيوك] إذا رأى أحد
[Laughing] Mr. Jay Do you think it's my boyfriend?
[يضحك] السيد جاي هل تعتقد أنه صديقي؟
The boss
الرئيس
[Meaningful music]
[موسيقى ذات معنى]
That's right, boyfriend.
هذا صحيح يا صديقها.
So you qualify?
إذن أنت مؤهل؟
I have the right to not let Jay drink alcohol.
لدي الحق في عدم السماح لجاي بشرب الكحول.
[Leo] Huh? [Laughter and exclamation]
[ليو] هاه؟ [ضحك وتعجب]
Sister Jae-i and brother Kang-hoo!
الأخت جاي آي والأخ كانغ هو!
It's 'Congratulation', hey, this is it
إنها "تهانينا"، هذا هو الأمر
It’s hotter than declaring candidacy.
إنه أكثر سخونة من إعلان الترشح.
[Haemi] Look, what did I say?
[هايمي] انظر ماذا قلت؟
He said no and said,
قال لا، فقال:
- [Haemi’s laughter] - [Leo] Now, now, now
- [ضحك هيمي] - [ليو] الآن، الآن، الآن
Brother, please sit down quickly.
أخي، من فضلك اجلس بسرعة.
So this time I, um
لذلك هذه المرة أنا، أم
Las Vegas style I'll roll it up for you
أسلوب لاس فيغاس سوف نشمر عنه بالنسبة لك
- [Haemi] Good - [Leo] Good
- [هيمي] جيد - [ليو] جيد
[Interesting music]
[موسيقى مثيرة للاهتمام]
[rattling sound]
[صوت قعقعة]
[Sound of pouring alcohol]
[صوت صب الكحول]
[Meaningful sound effects]
[مؤثرات صوتية ذات معنى]
[Yuncheol] Thank you for your hard work
[يونتشيول] شكرًا لك على عملك الجاد
[Yuna] Did you see it? Dojae
[يونا] هل رأيت ذلك؟ دوجاي
Were you surprised to see the congressman?
هل تفاجأت برؤية عضو الكونجرس؟
[Yuncheol] Well
[يونتشول] حسنًا
I think I'm a little surprised
أعتقد أنني مندهش قليلا
But what?
ولكن ماذا؟
That killed my son I don't think that means
الذي قتل ابني لا أعتقد أن هذا يعني
Jay has changed a lot.
لقد تغير جاي كثيرًا.
[Yuna] It used to be like that I wasn't shameless
[يونا] كان الأمر هكذا لم أكن وقحا
[Yuncheol] I heard you If you think you believe it 100%
[يونتشول] سمعتك إذا كنت تعتقد أنك تصدق ذلك 100%
It's an illusion
إنه وهم
the police obviously
الشرطة بشكل واضح
They said you were the criminal
قالوا أنك المجرم
my son last The person who sent the text
ابني الاخير الشخص الذي أرسل النص
It was you
لقد كان أنت
And on the spot You said your stuff was found too?
وعلى الفور قلت أنه تم العثور على الأشياء الخاصة بك أيضا؟
- [Meaningful music] - It's a trap.
- [موسيقى ذات معنى] - إنه فخ.
Someone is trying to make me a criminal
شخص ما يحاول أن يجعلني مجرمًا
Who?
من؟
[Yuncheol’s absurd laughter]
[ضحكة يونتشيول السخيفة]
[Yuncheol] Hey, this
[يونتشيول] مهلا، هذا
You have a very Pacific imagination. Huh?
لديك خيال المحيط الهادئ للغاية. هاه؟
Even if I search the whole world
حتى لو بحثت في العالم كله
I want to find the real culprit This is how the father feels.
أريد العثور على الجاني الحقيقي هكذا يشعر الأب.
It's not just Abby.
انها ليست مجرد آبي.
- [Yuna] Rep. Ki Yun-cheol - [Soaring music]
- [يونا] النائب كي يون تشيول - [موسيقى صاخبة]
My son died anyway
مات ابني على أية حال
If you think about your future political actions
إذا كنت تفكر في تصرفاتك السياسية المستقبلية
likes to ask and argue Rather than a lawyer
يحب أن يسأل ويجادل بدلا من المحامي
An easy-going bar girl Being a criminal
فتاة حانة سهلة كونه مجرماً
Wasn't it better?
ألم يكن أفضل؟
But are you going to start a full-fledged presidential election?
لكن هل ستبدأ انتخابات رئاسية كاملة؟
Even that must have been annoying?
حتى هذا يجب أن يكون مزعجا؟
Get me out of jail So much so that they are kicked out of this land.
أخرجوني من السجن لدرجة أنهم طردوا من هذه الأرض.
[Disapproving exclamation]
[علامة تعجب مستنكرة]
[Yuna] Are you telling me to leave?
[يونا] هل تطلب مني المغادرة؟
[Secretary Choi] What the old man said
[السكرتير تشوي] ما قاله الرجل العجوز
I'm just passing it on.
أنا فقط أنقلها.
[Yuncheol] So
[يونتشول] إذن
Why did you come to me?
لماذا أتيت إلي؟
Let’s reinvestigate it now
دعونا نعيد التحقيق في الأمر الآن
I want Do Jae-i to be put in jail. Do you want to say something?
أريد أن يتم وضع دو جاي في السجن. هل تريد أن تقول شيئا؟
[Yuna] No
[يونا] لا
I will take revenge on Dojae.
سوف أنتقم من دوجاي.
For a big guy like you I have to accept something bigger
لرجل كبير مثلك لا بد لي من قبول شيء أكبر
[absurd gasping sound]
[صوت يلهث سخيف]
[laughter]
[ضحك]
[Yuncheol] You want to keep me as insurance I think it's a masterpiece
[يونتشيول] تريد الاحتفاظ بي كتأمين أعتقد أنها تحفة فنية
What if you don’t like it?
ماذا لو كنت لا تحب ذلك؟
I can't do it
لا أستطيع أن أفعل ذلك
your son in the grave There is no choice but to take out the corpse.
ابنك في القبر ليس هناك خيار سوى إخراج الجثة.
[Yuna] Then your son What kind of guy was he
[يونا] ثم ابنك أي نوع من الرجل كان هو
What did you do that led to your death?
ماذا فعلت وأدى إلى وفاتك؟
It will be revealed to the world
سيتم الكشف عنها للعالم
Rep. Ki Yun-cheol, the next presidential candidate
النائب كي يون تشيول، المرشح الرئاسي القادم
To Grand Gangbo Hotel Could you take me there?
إلى فندق جراند جانجبو هل يمكن أن تأخذني إلى هناك؟
I'm there I'm staying in a suite.
أنا هناك أنا أقيم في جناح.
The place where Rep. Ki’s son died
المكان الذي توفي فيه ابن النائب كي
[Yuna’s laughter]
[ضحكة يونا]
[Door bell sounds]
[أصوات جرس الباب]
[Call connection tone]
[نغمة اتصال المكالمة]
[Yongpil] Attorney
[يونغبيل] المحامي
I checked and It is best sold at a local stationery store.
لقد راجعت و من الأفضل بيعه في متجر قرطاسية محلي.
There is nothing strange about the owner either. I don't think there is one
لا يوجد شيء غريب في المالك أيضًا. لا أعتقد أن هناك واحد
- [Sighing] Yes. - [Elegant music plays]
- [تنهد] نعم. - [تشغيل الموسيقى الأنيقة]
Okay, thank you for your hard work.
حسنا، شكرا لك على عملك الشاق.
[Yoojeong] I mean Leo.
[يوجيونغ] أعني ليو.
- It was like that earlier. - [glass clattering sound]
- كان الأمر كذلك في وقت سابق. - [صوت قعقعة الزجاج]
What's worse is that Mr. Kang-hoo appears.
والأمر الأسوأ هو ظهور السيد كانغ هوو.
[Bewildered] Oh my
[حائرة] يا بلدي
What made Kang-hoo angry was Is it because of Jehyuk?
ما أثار غضب كانغ هو هو هل هو بسبب جيهيوك؟
[Haemi] I thought the two of you were going to have a fight earlier.
[هايمي] اعتقدت أنكما ستتقاتلان في وقت سابق.
[Sigh] That’s our Jehyuk
[تنهد] هذا هو جيهيوك الخاص بنا
It's because I'm trying to accommodate Mr. Leo.
هذا لأنني أحاول استيعاب السيد ليو.
Guess our Leo?
تخمين ليو لدينا؟
Guess what?
خمين ما؟
- [Haemi] I’ve felt this for a long time. - [Sound of putting down a glass]
- [هيمي] لقد شعرت بهذا منذ فترة طويلة. - [صوت وضع كأس]
you secretly Do you know that we are ignoring Leo?
لك سرا هل تعلم أننا نتجاهل ليو؟
how many times have i We were supposed to have a couple's get-together, but they threw it away.
كم مرة قمت بذلك كان من المفترض أن نقيم لقاءً ثنائيًا، لكنهم تخلوا عنه.
I didn't like it
لم يعجبني ذلك
Our Leo Meeting Jehyuk in the same class
ليو لدينا لقاء جيهيوك في نفس الفصل
[Haemi and Yujeong laugh]
[هايمي ويوجيونج يضحكون]
Where is that word?
أين تلك الكلمة؟
That's just
هذا فقط
Jay doesn't have a boyfriend.
جاي ليس لديه صديق.
[Yoojeong] Between us Having a meeting like that
[يوجيونغ] بيننا عقد مثل هذا الاجتماع
I feel a bit sorry...
أشعر بالأسف قليلاً..
Hey, don't lie, I can see it all
مهلا، لا تكذب، أستطيع أن أرى كل شيء
[Haemi] You know that, right?
[هيمي] أنت تعرف ذلك، أليس كذلك؟
Pork belly or pork belly Are they all the same pork?
بطن لحم الخنزير أو بطن لحم الخنزير هل كلهم نفس لحم الخنزير؟
Leona Jehyuk In the end, it's all the same
ليونا جيهيوك في النهاية، كل شيء هو نفسه
Sticking a straw in a woman's back
لصق القش في ظهر المرأة
Have you said everything?
هل قلت كل شيء؟
[Making a yawning sound] No I didn't do it all
[إصدار صوت تثاؤب] لا لم أفعل كل شيء
[Haemi] I saw you earlier, Jehyuk.
[هيمي] رأيتك سابقًا يا جيهيوك.
He had talent
كان لديه موهبة
'Do I look like a man, do I?'
"هل أبدو كرجل، أليس كذلك؟"
- [Haemi’s snort] - [Sigh]
- [شخير هيمي] - [تنهد]
[Haemi] Do your research well before getting married.
[هايمي] قم بالبحث جيدًا قبل الزواج.
With that ironclad talent Is there a child hidden somewhere?
بتلك الموهبة الحديدية هل هناك طفل مختبئ في مكان ما؟
[Jay] Why did you do that earlier?
[جاي] لماذا فعلت ذلك في وقت سابق؟
He's my boyfriend
إنه صديقي
just
فقط
[Kanghu] Give me something I think it's rude
[كانغو] أعطني شيئا أعتقد أنه وقحا
You hate rude people
أنت تكره الناس وقحا
[Calm music]
[موسيقى هادئة]
Why?
لماذا؟
what?
ماذا؟
Why do you look at me like that?
لماذا تنظر إلي هكذا؟
[light laughter]
[ضحكة خفيفة]
Thank you for helping me
شكرا لمساعدتي
[Sighing] But
[تنهد] ولكن
It's true that I'm sensitive today
صحيح أنني حساس اليوم
[Jay] Just a drink I just had to drink it away.
[جاي] مجرد مشروب كان علي فقط أن أشربه بعيدًا.
[sigh]
[تنهد]
Why are you sensitive today?
لماذا أنت حساس اليوم؟
Earlier, at the nursery
في وقت سابق، في الحضانة
I saw that mask
رأيت ذلك القناع
[Jay's sigh]
[تنهد جاي]
How surprised I was
كم كنت متفاجئًا
A child wearing a mask
طفل يرتدي قناعا
I mistook it for that guy.
لقد أخطأت في ذلك بالنسبة لهذا الرجل.
Like a fool
مثل أحمق
[Looking embarrassed] No
[تبدو محرجة] لا
Well, it just looked the same.
حسنا، لقد بدا الأمر نفسه.
[Jay] The material is different too The mark is also different
[جاي] المادة مختلفة أيضًا العلامة مختلفة أيضًا
[Laughing] It was a different mask.
[يضحك] لقد كان قناعًا مختلفًا.
Is it because the statute of limitations is running out?
هل لأن مدة التقادم قد انتهت؟
Just
فقط
I'm getting impatient
أنا أشعر بفارغ الصبر
[sigh]
[تنهد]
Jay
جاي
Maybe I can catch him If there's anything I can help you with...
ربما أستطيع القبض عليه إذا كان هناك أي شيء أستطيع مساعدتك به...
[Meaningful sound effects]
[مؤثرات صوتية ذات معنى]
Leo went to light a cigarette. I want to give you some company.
ذهب ليو لإشعال سيجارة. أريد أن أعطيك بعض الشركات.
[Jehyuk] Two people Congratulations again
[جيهيوك] شخصان تهانينا مرة أخرى
[Meaningful music]
[موسيقى ذات معنى]
[sigh]
[تنهد]
Jehyuk must be a good person.
يجب أن يكون جيهيوك شخصًا جيدًا.
[Laughing] Well, leaving everything else aside
[يضحك] حسنًا، اترك كل شيء آخر جانبًا
Yoojeong
يوجيونغ
I like Jehyuk a lot
أنا أحب جيهيوك كثيرا
So, Mr. Kang-hoo
إذن يا سيد كانغ هو
relax your mind
استرخي عقلك
[sigh]
[تنهد]
[Leo] Uh, bro
[ليو] اه، وإخوانه
I've been thinking about it
لقد كنت أفكر في ذلك
I'll go back to work as my brother said.
سأعود للعمل كما قال أخي.
But
لكن
On the condition of administering medication rather than being an athlete.
بشرط إعطاء الدواء بدلاً من أن تكون رياضياً.
instead brother
بدلا من ذلك أخي
You better really watch your mouth.
من الأفضل أن تراقب فمك حقًا.
uh
اه
[Cell phone operation sound]
[صوت تشغيل الهاتف الخليوي]
[Leo’s sigh]
[تنهد ليو]
[Leo clicks his tongue]
[ينقر ليو على لسانه]
Boy, tsk
فتى، تسك
- [Joyful music] - 'Thank you'
- [موسيقى بهيجة] - "شكرا لك"
But did you smoke?
لكن هل دخنت؟
From what I heard from Hae-mi, I can't even drink well
مما سمعته من هاي مي، لا أستطيع حتى أن أشرب جيدا
Saenim doesn’t even smoke…
سينيم لا يدخن حتى…
- [Laughs] - [Leo laughs] A nerd, a nerd
- [يضحك] - [يضحك ليو] الطالب الذي يذاكر كثيرا، الطالب الذي يذاكر كثيرا
Everyone has a secret
كل شخص لديه سر
Especially to the wife-to-be
وخاصة لزوجة المستقبل
I didn't tell Yujeong. What's the secret?
أنا لم أخبر يوجيونغ. ما هو السر؟
[Jehyuk] What about Leo?
[جيهيوك] ماذا عن ليو؟
Does Haemi have a secret?
هل لدى هيمي سر؟
[Leo's gulping sound]
[صوت ابتلاع ليو]
[Leo] Ah I thought I had it all figured out
[ليو] آه اعتقدت أنني قد اكتشفت كل شيء
[Clicking tongue] Now again It seems like it will happen, sadly
[النقر باللسان] الآن مرة أخرى يبدو أن ذلك سيحدث، للأسف
What is that?
ما هذا؟
What that means is that this time I
ما يعنيه ذلك هو أنني هذه المرة
[surprised elasticity]
[مرونة مفاجئة]
Because it comes naturally I almost said everything
لأنه يأتي بشكل طبيعي قلت كل شيء تقريبا
- [Leo] This brother is a player, a player. - [Laughs]
- [ليو] هذا الأخ لاعب، لاعب. - [يضحك]
[Laughing] Then let's not talk to each other
[يضحك] ثم دعونا لا نتحدث مع بعضنا البعض
[Jehyuk] When a secret is a secret Because it's fun
[جيهيوك] عندما يكون السر سرًا لأنه ممتع
If all the secrets are revealed All the fun is gone
إذا تم الكشف عن جميع الأسرار لقد ذهبت كل المتعة
like smoke
مثل الدخان
[Then exhales]
[ثم يزفر]
[Jehyuk’s laughter]
[ضحكة جيهيوك]
[Nana, babysitter’s laughter]
[نانا، ضحكة جليسة الأطفال]
[Babysitter] Is it fun? uh?
[جليسة أطفال] هل هذا ممتع؟ أوه؟
[Babysitter's playful mouth sounds]
[أصوات فم جليسة الأطفال المرحة]
- ‘Go’, ‘Go’, ‘Go’, is it fun? - [Nana and the babysitter’s laughter]
- "اذهب"، "اذهب"، "اذهب"، هل هذا ممتع؟ - [ضحكة نانا والجليسة]
Wow [laughs]
واو [يضحك]
You've grown a lot
لقد كبرت كثيرًا
my baby
طفلي
- [Mobile phone ringing sound] - [Woman 1 laughs]
- [صوت رنين الهاتف المحمول] - [المرأة 1 تضحك]
- [Mobile phone operation sound] - [Babysitter] Oh, hello.
- [صوت تشغيل الهاتف المحمول] - [جليسة الأطفال] أوه، مرحباً.
Oh, what day?
أوه، أي يوم؟
Oh, I see.
أوه، أرى.
[Laughing] Oh my What did you not think of?
[يضحك] يا إلهي ما الذي لم تفكر فيه؟
[dark music]
[الموسيقى المظلمة]
[worried breathing]
[التنفس القلق]
[Old] Emily, ‘Welcome to Korea’
[قديم] إميلي، "مرحبًا بك في كوريا"
[old-fashioned laughter]
[ضحكة قديمة]
[Old-fashioned squeak]
[صرير الطراز القديم]
the person I found
الشخص الذي وجدته
You're the kid's dad, right?
أنت والد الطفل، أليس كذلك؟
[panicked breathing]
[التنفس المذعور]
yes
نعم
how
كيف
Are you going to meet me?
هل ستقابلني؟
We have to meet
علينا أن نلتقي
We have to meet and end it.
علينا أن نلتقي وننهي الأمر.
[Old-fashioned gulping sound]
[صوت البلع القديم]
I don't think it will be easy? finish it off
لا أعتقد أن الأمر سيكون سهلاً؟ الانتهاء منه
[Old] Huh?
[قديم] هاه؟
There was a back boat That's huge too
كان هناك قارب خلفي هذا ضخم أيضًا
Back belly?
البطن الخلفي؟
Not only the child's father He said he had to find his child.
وليس والد الطفل فقط وقال إنه يجب أن يجد طفله.
Well, if you go out carelessly, I think it's dangerous
حسنًا، إذا خرجت بلا مبالاة، أعتقد أن هذا خطير
Let alone the kid who attacked you wrongly.
ناهيك عن الطفل الذي هاجمك خطأً.
Should I rot in prison for the rest of my life?
هل يجب أن أتعفن في السجن لبقية حياتي؟
- [wind sound] - [Crying breathing]
- [صوت الريح] - [تنفس البكاء]
[sigh]
[تنهد]
[Babysitter] Uh, uh
[جليسة الأطفال] اه، اه
[Babysitter laughs]
[تضحك جليسة الأطفال]
[Yuna’s crying, breathing sound]
[يونا تبكي، صوت التنفس]
- [surprised gasp] - [Woman 1] Oh, my.
- [شهقة مستغربة] - [المرأة 1] يا إلهي.
Oh my, oh my, oh my Wow, ah
يا بلدي، يا بلدي، يا بلدي واو، اه
[Sigh of relief]
[تنهد من الإغاثة]
[sigh]
[تنهد]
Fish oil [surprised gasp]
زيت السمك [لهث متفاجئ]
You have to be careful when riding
عليك أن تكون حذرا عند الركوب
- [Nana] Thank you - [Woman 1] Oh, ride carefully.
- [نانا] شكرا لك - [المرأة 1] أوه، اركب بحذر.
[Babysitter] Yeah, yeah
[جليسة الأطفال] نعم، نعم
[Sound of paper rustling]
[صوت حفيف الورق]
[Babysitter] Oh, yeah, yeah Okay
[جليسة الأطفال] أوه، نعم، نعم حسنا
[Cell phone operation sound]
[صوت تشغيل الهاتف الخليوي]
[Babysitter's surprised gasp]
[شهقة جليسة الأطفال المفاجئة]
Who gave you this?
من أعطاك هذا؟
[Woman 2] The person over there…
[المرأة 2] الشخص هناك...
[Sound of tapping feet]
[صوت نقر الأقدام]
[Sound of Yuna’s footsteps moving away]
[صوت خطى يونا تبتعد]
[Yoojeong] I’ll go first, I’ll go first
[يوجيونغ] سأذهب أولاً، سأذهب أولاً
- [Jehyuk] See you again - [Haemi] Go in
- [جيهيوك] نراكم مرة أخرى - [هايمي] ادخل
- [Jay] Go in - [Leo] Yes, please go in.
- [جاي] ادخل - [ليو] نعم، من فضلك ادخل.
[Car engine sound]
[صوت محرك السيارة]
[Sound of car door closing]
[صوت إغلاق باب السيارة]
[Haemi] The two of them What are you going to do now?
[هيمي] الاثنان منهم ماذا ستفعل الآن؟
It's the 1st from today.
إنه الأول من اليوم.
- [Haemi’s light laughter] - [Jay] Ayu
- [ضحكة هيمي الخفيفة] - [جاي] أيو
Don't talk nonsense and get on quickly.
لا تتحدث بالهراء وامضي قدماً بسرعة.
[Leo] Brother, good luck. [Laughs]
[ليو] أخي، حظا سعيدا. [يضحك]
[Sound of car door opening]
[صوت فتح باب السيارة]
Kang-hoo, fighting!
كانغ هوو، القتال!
- [Haemi’s laughter] - [Jay] Go in
- [ضحك هيمي] - [جاي] ادخل
[Sound of car door closing]
[صوت إغلاق باب السيارة]
[Car engine sound receding]
[انحسار صوت محرك السيارة]
Do you want to come in for a moment?
هل تريد الدخول للحظة؟
- [Calm music] - [Kanghu] Oh, well, over there, what
- [موسيقى هادئة] - [كانغو] أوه، حسنًا، هناك، ماذا
You didn’t eat well earlier.
أنت لم تأكل جيدا في وقت سابق.
There was also food left
وكان هناك أيضا طعام متبقي
[light laughter]
[ضحكة خفيفة]
Is that so?
هل هذا صحيح؟
[Kanghu’s light smile]
[ابتسامة كانغو الخفيفة]
Why did you do that earlier?
لماذا فعلت ذلك في وقت سابق؟
[Yoojeong] Earlier, at the drinking party
[Yoojeong] في وقت سابق، في حفل الشرب
He seemed like a slightly different person.
لقد بدا وكأنه شخص مختلف قليلاً.
Playing mischievous pranks
لعب المقالب المؤذية
[breath mixed with laughter]
[نفس ممزوج بالضحك]
me
أنا
I like pranks
أنا أحب المزح
[Yujeong and Jehyuk’s laughter]
[ضحكة يوجيونغ وجيهيوك]
I tried
حاولت
[Jehyuk] To set the tension with Leo
[جيهيوك] لضبط التوتر مع ليو
I'm calming down
أنا أهدأ
Hae-mi’s position is a bit like that.
موقف هاي مي يشبه ذلك قليلاً.
I would already care about my husband’s background.
سأهتم بالفعل بخلفية زوجي.
[light laughter]
[ضحكة خفيفة]
Right?
أليس كذلك؟
Is that so?
هل هذا صحيح؟
[breath mixed with laughter]
[نفس ممزوج بالضحك]
As expected
كما هو متوقع
[Yujeong] Your consideration
[Yujeong] اعتبارك
Why did you do that, Mr. Yujeong?
لماذا فعلت ذلك يا سيد يوجيونغ؟
Jae-i and Kang-hoo are doing well.
جاي آي وكانغ هو في حالة جيدة.
I felt like I didn't like it very much.
شعرت أنني لم أحب ذلك كثيرًا.
Uh [embarrassed breathing]
اه [التنفس بالحرج]
That…
أن…
No, nothing like that.
لا، لا شيء من هذا القبيل.
[Jehyuk] Tell me
[جيهيوك] أخبرني
before we got married You said there would be no secrets.
قبل أن نتزوج قلت أنه لن يكون هناك أسرار.
[light sigh]
[تنهد خفيف]
Actually
في الواقع
Kang-hoo's girlfriend
صديقة كانغ هوو
We were friends from back in the day
كنا أصدقاء من الخلف في اليوم
But Jae-yi
لكن جاي يي
Doing that with that friend's ex-boyfriend?
هل تفعل ذلك مع صديقها السابق؟
[Exhaling in disgust] It's so terrible.
[زفر باشمئزاز] إنه أمر فظيع للغاية.
I can't do that
لا أستطيع أن أفعل ذلك
[Yujeong’s sigh]
[تنهد يوجيونغ]
Such a terrible friend
مثل هذا الصديق الرهيب
Who are you?
من أنت؟
You don’t need to know [Awkward laughter]
لا تحتاج أن تعرف [ضحك محرج]
Mr. Jehyuk I'm a person you'll never see.
السيد جيهيوك أنا شخص لن تراه أبدًا.
[Yujeong’s breathing mixed with laughter]
[تنفس يوجيونج ممزوج بالضحك]
[Jehyuk’s light smile]
[ابتسامة جيهيوك الخفيفة]
[Leo] Jehyuk hyung.
[ليو] جيهيوك هيونغ.
[Haemi] Jehyuk, what?
[هايمي] جيهيوك، ماذا؟
Before I got a job at Yujeong’s sister’s daycare center.
قبل أن أحصل على وظيفة في مركز الرعاية النهارية التابع لأخت يوجيونغ.
I guess it was because he was a person who did something?
أعتقد أنه كان لأنه كان الشخص الذي فعل شيئا؟
[Laughing] I don’t know.
[تضحك] لا أعرف.
I heard you were a teacher I don't watch anymore because I'm bored, why?
سمعت أنك كنت مدرسا لم أعد أشاهد لأنني أشعر بالملل، لماذا؟
[Meaningful music]
[موسيقى ذات معنى]
Huh? 'Thank you'
هاه؟ شكرا لك
I don't think he has the manners of an ordinary person.
لا أعتقد أن لديه أخلاق أي شخص عادي.
What?
ماذا؟
[Leo] That brother was earlier He gives me a cigarette...
[ليو] كان هذا الأخ في وقت سابق يعطيني سيجارة..
[cell phone vibrates]
[يهتز الهاتف الخليوي]
What is it?
ما هذا؟
Uh, nothing.
اه، لا شيء.
Jehyuk, what about cigarettes? Didn't you?
جيهيوك ماذا عن السجائر؟ أليس كذلك؟
uh
اه
I just think he’s a person with good manners.
أعتقد فقط أنه شخص ذو أخلاق جيدة.
[Bewildered] What?
[في حيرة] ماذا؟
[Haemi] It’s Leo
[هايمي] إنه ليو
When I get home, get some sleep first.
عندما أعود إلى المنزل، احصل على قسط من النوم أولاً.
Shaved ice for my hotel Because I have to think about it all night
حلق الجليد لفندقي لأنني يجب أن أفكر في الأمر طوال الليل
[Leo] No way, sister
[ليو] مستحيل يا أختي
I wonder if I have to stay all night again...
أتساءل عما إذا كان علي أن أبقى طوال الليل مرة أخرى ...
I told you not to talk nonsense, right?
قلت لك ألا تتحدث هراء، أليس كذلك؟
[Haemi] No, please be quiet.
[هيمي] لا، من فضلك كن هادئا.
Because I need to get some sleep
لأنني بحاجة للحصول على بعض النوم
[Meaningful sound effects]
[مؤثرات صوتية ذات معنى]
[Yuna] Behind?
[يونا] خلف؟
[Old] Not only the child’s father Are you saying I need to find my child?
[قديم] ليس والد الطفل فقط هل تقول أنني بحاجة للعثور على طفلي؟
Well, if you go out carelessly, I think it's dangerous
حسنًا، إذا خرجت بلا مبالاة، أعتقد أن هذا خطير
Let alone the kid who attacked you wrongly.
ناهيك عن الطفل الذي هاجمك خطأً.
Should I rot in prison for the rest of my life?
هل يجب أن أتعفن في السجن لبقية حياتي؟
[Old-fashioned gulping sound]
[صوت البلع القديم]
[Old-fashioned breathing sound]
[صوت التنفس القديم]
So
هكذا
Get ready and attack
الاستعداد والهجوم
To that guy
إلى ذلك الرجل
[light sigh]
[تنهد خفيف]
What the heck
ما هيك
A person called Backbae How great of a person is he?
شخص يدعى باكباي كم هو عظيم هذا الشخص؟
[Meaningful music]
[موسيقى ذات معنى]
[Old] That's
[قديم] هذا
I take good care of my land
أنا أعتني جيدًا بأرضي
If I give it back after I become minister I'll tell you then
إذا أرجعتها بعد أن أصبح وزيرا سأخبرك بعد ذلك
Later, Emily If you just get land and run away, you're in trouble.
في وقت لاحق، إميلي إذا حصلت على الأرض وهربت، فأنت في ورطة.
[old-fashioned laughter]
[ضحكة قديمة]
[Heavy sound effect]
[مؤثرات صوتية ثقيلة]
[Elegant music plays]
[تشغيل الموسيقى الأنيقة]
[light laughter]
[ضحكة خفيفة]
[Sound of Ganghu gulping bitterly]
[صوت جانجو وهو يبتلع بمرارة]
[cell phone vibrates]
[يهتز الهاتف الخليوي]
Yes, manager.
نعم أيها المدير.
- [Nervous music] - [Sound of door opening]
- [موسيقى عصبية] - [صوت فتح الباب]
- [Kanghu] The taxi will arrive soon. - [Jay] Yes
- [كانغو] ستصل سيارة الأجرة قريبًا. - [جاي] نعم
- [Kanghu] Ah - [Jay’s sigh]
- [كانغو] آه - [تنهد جاي]
[Oncoming car driving sound]
[صوت قيادة السيارة القادمة]
Hey, is it okay if I don’t go with you?
مهلا، هل هو بخير إذا لم أذهب معك؟
Uh, it's okay
اه، لا بأس
[Kanghu] Be careful
[كانغو] كن حذرا
[Light laughter] I will
[ضحكة خفيفة] سأفعل
[sigh]
[تنهد]
[Soaring music]
[موسيقى صاخبة]
[Jay] Yes, manager.
[جاي] نعم، مدير.
I'm on my way to the police station now.
أنا في طريقي إلى مركز الشرطة الآن.
But
لكن
Are you sure about that mask?
هل أنت متأكد من هذا القناع؟
In the words of the chief I raided an illegal gambling house.
على لسان الزعيم لقد قمت بمداهمة منزل قمار غير قانوني.
The characteristics of the gambling hall are They said it was to wear a mask.
خصائص قاعة القمار هي قالوا أنه كان يرتدي قناعا.
[Yongpil] But one of the guests I was wearing that mask
[يونغبيل] لكن أحد الضيوف كنت أرتدي هذا القناع
Really?
حقا؟
Then who is the person wearing the mask?
إذن من هو الشخص الذي يرتدي القناع؟
Did you find out?
هل اكتشفت ذلك؟
[Noisy noise]
[ضوضاء صاخبة]
[telephone ringing sound]
[صوت رنين الهاتف]
[Continued phone ringing]
[استمرار رنين الهاتف]
[Noisy noise]
[ضوضاء صاخبة]
- [walkie-talkie sound] - [Noisy sound]
- [صوت جهاز الاتصال اللاسلكي] - [صوت مزعج]
[nervous music]
[موسيقى عصبية]
[Bomi] Judge
[بومي] القاضي
That file is
هذا الملف هو
I told Attorney Do Jae-i borrow a watch
لقد أخبرت المحامي دو جاي آي استعارة ساعة
It's true that I recorded it myself.
صحيح أنني سجلت ذلك بنفسي.
[Sound of intake of breath]
[صوت أخذ نفس]
[Jay] This mask
[جاي] هذا القناع
What happened?
ماذا حدث؟
Every time I feel stressed
في كل مرة أشعر بالتوتر
I need stimulating play
أحتاج إلى تحفيز اللعب
[Bomi] But Attorney Jae-yi Do You interrupted my play.
[بومي] لكن المحامي جاي يي دو لقد قاطعت مسرحيتي.
[Jay] Where did you get it?
[جاي] من أين حصلت عليه؟
Why can't I steal something from someone else? I stole my husband's baby
لماذا لا أستطيع سرقة شيء من شخص آخر؟ لقد سرقت طفل زوجي
[Bomi’s laughter]
[ضحك بومي]
[Bomi] That bastard now Falsely accused of rape
[بومي] هذا اللقيط الآن اتهم زورا بالاغتصاب
I'm in the detention center.
أنا في مركز الاحتجاز.
Because of you
بسببك
Mr. Kim Man-bok
السيد كيم مان بوك
- [Bomi’s candy sucking sound] - How did you get this?
- [صوت مص الحلوى لبومي] - كيف حصلت على هذا؟
I heard you get it if you join some club.
سمعت أنك ستحصل عليه إذا انضممت إلى بعض الأندية.
[Bomi] Ah
[بومي] آه
This club closed 10 years ago.
تم إغلاق هذا النادي منذ 10 سنوات.
- I thought it was reopening? - [Tense sound effect]
- اعتقدت أنه تم إعادة فتحه؟ - [تأثير صوتي متوتر]
Is it open again?
هل هو مفتوح مرة أخرى؟
[Old] I did it 10 years ago
[قديم] لقد فعلت ذلك منذ 10 سنوات
of some club I signed up for membership
من بعض الأندية لقد قمت بالتسجيل للحصول على العضوية
The club's meeting place is Because it's there
مكان اجتماع النادي هو لأنه هناك
[dark music]
[الموسيقى المظلمة]
the club
النادي
Do you know where it is?
هل تعرف أين هو؟
To Choi Bomi Did you hear the club location?
إلى تشوي بومي هل سمعت بموقع النادي؟
no
لا
Kim Man-bok even to Choi Bomi They say they kept it a secret.
كيم مان بوك حتى لتشوي بومي يقولون أنهم أبقوا الأمر سرا.
[Jay] It’s definitely out there somewhere.
[جاي] إنه بالتأكيد موجود في مكان ما.
I don't know where it is It's so frustrating
لا أعرف أين هو إنه أمر محبط للغاية
The club closed 10 years ago Why reopen?
تم إغلاق النادي منذ 10 سنوات لماذا إعادة فتح؟
Maybe
ربما
prayer ceremony incident Could it be related?
حادثة صلاة هل يمكن أن تكون ذات صلة؟
[dark music]
[الموسيقى المظلمة]
Even if everyone in the world says no
حتى لو قال كل شخص في العالم لا
You know it yourself
أنت تعرف ذلك بنفسك
That I saw the mask
أنني رأيت القناع
Then, until the incident quiets down. Have you been struggling for 10 years?
ثم حتى يهدأ الحادث. هل كنت تكافح لمدة 10 سنوات؟
In 10 years
في 10 سنوات
for rape Because the statute of limitations has expired.
للاغتصاب لأن مدة التقادم قد انتهت.
If that guess is correct
إذا كان هذا التخمين صحيحا
He's in that club Could be a key figure
إنه في ذلك النادي يمكن أن يكون شخصية رئيسية
Close the club able to reopen
اغلاق النادي قادرة على إعادة فتح
I guess I'll go there myself I need to peck at Kim Man-bok.
أعتقد أنني سأذهب إلى هناك بنفسي أحتاج إلى النقر على كيم مان بوك.
And the lawyer
والمحامي
[Yongpil] Look at this
[يونغبيل] انظر إلى هذا
[Jay laughs]
[جاي يضحك]
In my declaration of candidacy I sent Ki Yun-cheol
في إعلان ترشحي لقد أرسلت كي يون تشيول
- I'm sure it's Go Yoo Na. - [Clock second hand sound effect]
- أنا متأكد من أنها جو يو نا. - [مؤثرات صوتية على مدار الساعة]
Keep following Go Yoo-na's footsteps.
استمر في اتباع خطى Go Yoo-na.
[Calm music plays]
[تشغيل الموسيقى الهادئة]
[Sound of foot massage]
[صوت تدليك القدم]
[Yun Cheol] Welcome, Chairman.
[يون تشيول] مرحباً، سيدي الرئيس.
[Sound of a group of people gulping bitterly]
[صوت مجموعة من الناس يبتلعون بمرارة]
[Ilgu] Why in a place like this? Did you ask to meet up?
[Ilgu] لماذا في مكان مثل هذا؟ هل طلبت اللقاء؟
[Laughing] I
[يضحك] أنا
I'm having some stress.
أواجه بعض التوتر.
[Yuncheol] You don’t have to worry
[يونتشيول] لا داعي للقلق
As you can see
كما ترون
They can't see us or hear us.
لا يمكنهم رؤيتنا أو سماعنا.
[Sound of glass pieces falling]
[صوت سقوط قطع الزجاج]
[laughter]
[ضحك]
[Yuncheol] Like this You are a thorough person.
[يونتشيول] مثل هذا أنت شخص دقيق.
To others so far
للآخرين حتى الآن
You probably haven't found a single weakness.
ربما لم تجد نقطة ضعف واحدة.
[Sniffing bitterly] But what should I do about this?
[استنشاق بمرارة] ولكن ماذا علي أن أفعل حيال ذلك؟
Go Yoo-na came to Korea
جاءت Go Yoo-na إلى كوريا
What did they say?
ماذا قالوا؟
He killed my son He's not the culprit?
لقد قتل ابني انه ليس الجاني؟
The culprit is
الجاني هو
I heard it's Dojae.
سمعت أنه دوجاي.
Fortunately, unique
لحسن الحظ، فريدة من نوعها
Dojae is the chairman's wife. I don't think I know
Dojae هي زوجة الرئيس. لا أعتقد أنني أعرف
[Yuncheol’s laughter]
[ضحكة يونتشيول]
- [Interesting Music] - [Yuncheol] That’s amazing too.
- [موسيقى مثيرة للاهتمام] - [يونتشيول] هذا مذهل أيضًا.
No matter how young and energetic I committed it, Even though it was a mistake
بغض النظر عن مدى شبابي وحيويتي التي ارتكبتها، على الرغم من أنه كان خطأ
In a world like today
في عالم مثل اليوم
how do you do that I wonder if it can be completely hidden [laughter]
كيف يمكنك أن تفعل ذلك أتساءل عما إذا كان من الممكن إخفاؤه بالكامل [ضحك]
Would you like me to clean it up for you? Go Yoo-na
هل تريد مني تنظيفه لك؟ اذهب يو نا
[Ilgu] Our Kangbo Group is
[Ilgu] مجموعتنا كانجبو هي
You are the most powerful person in this country. What I make for you
أنت أقوى شخص في هذا البلد. ما أصنعه لك
It is the calling of a lifetime.
إنها نداء العمر.
But
لكن
How dare a girl like that
كيف تجرؤ فتاة مثل هذا
Rep.'s shameful son If you try to find out
ابن النائب المخزي إذا حاولت معرفة ذلك
I have to clean it up, I
يجب أن أنظفه، أنا
[Light laughter] No.
[ضحكة خفيفة] لا.
As the Chairman said
كما قال الرئيس
That kind of girl
هذا النوع من الفتاة
What can you dare to do?
ماذا يمكنك أن تجرؤ على القيام به؟
[Yuncheol] Just Knowing it is revelation
[يونتشول] فقط ومعرفته هو الوحي
Then
ثم
I hope you relieve your stress well
أتمنى أن تخفف من التوتر بشكل جيد
- [Sound of a group of people slurping bitterly] - [Meaningful music]
- [صوت مجموعة من الناس يلتهمون بمرارة] - [موسيقى ذات معنى]
I don't fit in like this
أنا لا تناسب مثل هذا
Well then, that's it
حسنا، هذا كل شيء
[Sound of a group of people breathing]
[صوت مجموعة من الناس يتنفسون]
[Exhales loudly]
[يزفر بصوت عالٍ]
[Junghyun] Still, the culprit was caught Thank goodness
[Junghyun] ومع ذلك، تم القبض على الجاني الحمد لله
I risk my life and death Found the culprit, yes
أنا أخاطر بحياتي وموتي لقد وجدت الجاني، نعم
[Siren sound heard from far away]
[سمع صوت صفارة الإنذار من بعيد]
[Yuncheol] Who is that woman?
[يونتشيول] من هي تلك المرأة؟
[Junghyun] Oh, I’m Attorney Jae-i Do.
[Junghyun] أوه، أنا المحامي جاي إي دو.
Until the bar madam got caught.
حتى تم القبض على سيدتي الحانة.
He was the most likely suspect.
وكان المشتبه به على الأرجح.
But
لكن
Why Kangbo Group Are you with Vice Chairman Kang Il-gu?
لماذا مجموعة كانجبو هل أنت مع نائب الرئيس كانغ إيل غو؟
That's strange to me too
وهذا غريب بالنسبة لي أيضا
Anyway, Vice Chairman Kang Il-gu After coming
على أية حال، نائب الرئيس كانغ إيل غو بعد مجيئه
The chief's order has been given.
لقد صدر أمر الرئيس.
[Junghyeon] The real culprit was caught too.
[Junghyeon] تم القبض على الجاني الحقيقي أيضًا.
Attorney Jae-i Do Don't investigate any further.
المحامي جاي دو لا تحقق أكثر من ذلك.
even
حتى
They even said to delete the records I had?
حتى أنهم قالوا لحذف السجلات التي كانت لدي؟
Well, isn’t that something like that? [laughter]
حسنًا، أليس هذا شيئًا من هذا القبيل؟ [ضحك]
Having a child out of wedlock, something like that?
إنجاب طفل خارج إطار الزواج، شيء من هذا القبيل؟
Fatherly love once
الحب الأبوي مرة واحدة
I'm crying
أنا أبكي
[Cell phone operation sound]
[صوت تشغيل الهاتف الخليوي]
- [Mobile phone operation sound] - [Yuncheol] Go Yoo-na
- [صوت تشغيل الهاتف المحمول] - [يونتشول] اذهب يو نا
If you need anything, let me know.
إذا كنت بحاجة إلى أي شيء، اسمحوا لي أن أعرف.
let me help you
اسمحوا لي أن أساعدك
[Text sending sound]
[صوت إرسال النص]
[heavy music]
[موسيقى ثقيلة]
[Taking a breath] You protect your daughter.
[يأخذ نفسا] أنت تحمي ابنتك.
I hunt my son's killer Because I will punish you
أنا أطارد قاتل ابني لأنني سوف أعاقبك
[Soaring music]
[موسيقى صاخبة]
[Meaningful music]
[موسيقى ذات معنى]
[Employee] Oh, hey.
[الموظف] أوه، مهلا.
This is a membership club.
هذا هو نادي العضوية.
And it's under construction Business is closed
وهو قيد الإنشاء العمل مغلق
[snort]
[شخير]
I'm going to change some chairs What is remodeling?
سأقوم بتغيير بعض الكراسي ما هو إعادة التصميم؟
[breathing sound]
[صوت التنفس]
I'm not a guest
أنا لست ضيفا
It's a partner company.
إنها شركة شريكة.
- [Meaningful music] - [Sound of bags rattling]
- [موسيقى ذات معنى] - [صوت قعقعة الحقائب]
Tell it to President Jeong.
أخبر ذلك للرئيس جيونج.
Go madam came
اذهبي سيدتي جاءت
[President Jeong] Oh my gosh
[الرئيس جيونج] يا إلهي
Who is this?
من هذا؟
no I heard you had a hard time at Kampang.
لا سمعت أنك واجهت وقتًا عصيبًا في كامبانغ.
Wow, is it because I can’t see the sunlight? Make your skin more shiny
واو، هل هذا لأنني لا أستطيع رؤية ضوء الشمس؟ اجعل بشرتك أكثر لمعانًا
Put away the nonsense
ضع بعيدا هذا الهراء
President Jeong [sighs]
الرئيس جيونج [تنهدات]
You know my ex-husband, right?
أنت تعرف زوجي السابق، أليس كذلك؟
Are you married?
هل أنت متزوج؟
No, who sees Madam Ko as a married woman?
لا، من يرى مدام كو امرأة متزوجة؟
Hey, even if I go to active duty right now...
مهلا، حتى لو ذهبت إلى الخدمة الفعلية الآن...
[slams the table]
[يضرب الطاولة]
[President Jeong] No Well, I heard about it.
[الرئيس جيونج] لا حسنا، سمعت عن ذلك.
Living together means
العيش معًا يعني
Oh, but I'm with that guy It's been a long time since we lost contact
أوه، ولكن أنا مع هذا الرجل لقد مر وقت طويل منذ أن فقدنا الاتصال
Oh, what, do you have dog habits?
أوه، ماذا، هل لديك عادات خاصة بالكلاب؟
어디 호구 년 하나 물어 가지고 들어앉았는지
كيفية الحصول على بطاقة الائتمان الخاصة بك شكرا جزيلا
코빼기도 안 보이더라고
هذا هو ما تبحث عنه
[유나] 내가 그 새끼가 Where do you live and what do you do?
[유나] 내가 그 새끼가 أين تعيش وماذا تفعل؟
Do you think I came here because I didn’t know?
هل تعتقد أنني أتيت إلى هنا لأنني لا أعرف؟
What I want to know
ما أريد أن أعرف
He's the big guy who looks after that bastard.
إنه الرجل الكبير الذي يعتني بهذا الوغد.
[President Jeong] Big guy?
[الرئيس جيونج] رجل كبير؟
Is the big guy watching your back?
هل الرجل الكبير يراقب ظهرك؟
Who is it?
من هذا؟
[absurd gasping sound]
[صوت يلهث سخيف]
[Exciting music]
[موسيقى مثيرة]
I still can't come to my senses
ما زلت لا أستطيع العودة إلى روحي
[Yuna] Even after 10 years, I
[يونا] حتى بعد 10 سنوات، أنا
It's Madam Go.
إنها سيدتي جو.
blow fast
ضربة سريعة
Let alone remodeling the store. before putting it out of business
ناهيك عن إعادة تصميم المتجر. قبل إخراجها من العمل
[Sound of footsteps coming down the stairs]
[صوت خطوات تنزل على الدرج]
[Sound of door opening]
[صوت فتح الباب]
- [Leo] Oh - [Sound of door closing]
- [ليو] أوه - [صوت إغلاق الباب]
Isn't it in President Jeong's office?
أليس في مكتب الرئيس جيونج؟
[Employee] Oh, are you with a customer right now?
[الموظف] أوه، هل أنت مع عميل الآن؟
The late Madame?
السيدة الراحلة؟
[eerie sound effect]
[مؤثرات صوتية غريبة]
[Manbok] What? Let's make a deal?
[مانبوك] ماذا؟ دعونا نعقد صفقة؟
So
هكذا
If I tell you where the club is
إذا أخبرتك بمكان النادي
Will you save my company?
هل ستنقذ شركتي؟
[full laughter]
[ضحك كامل]
No, what are you doing? Are you going to ruin my company?
لا، ماذا تفعل؟ هل ستدمر شركتي؟
Your wife Choi Bomi
زوجتك تشوي بومي
Playing at an unlicensed gambling house I got caught
اللعب في بيت قمار غير مرخص لقد تم القبض علي
Mr.
السيد
[Manbok] Is this guy’s wife crazy?
[مانبوك] هل زوجة هذا الرجل مجنونة؟
From stealing to now gambling
من السرقة إلى المقامرة الآن
Because of you It's already a risky company
بسببك إنها بالفعل شركة محفوفة بالمخاطر
[Jay] No, if your wife gets robbed
[جاي] لا، إذا تعرضت زوجتك للسرقة
Who would buy that company's products?
من سيشتري منتجات تلك الشركة؟
Well, sales will drop.
حسنًا، سوف تنخفض المبيعات.
Well then, you're screwed.
حسنا، أنت ثمل.
[Embarrassing sound]
[صوت محرج]
[Manbok’s voice of worry]
[صوت مانبوك القلق]
[Jay] So
[جاي] إذن
Talk to me
تحدث معي
Where is the club?
أين هو النادي؟
good
جيد
Look forward to it
نتطلع إلى ذلك
Tomorrow on the front of the portal Because your wife will be plastered with articles.
غدا على واجهة البوابة لأن زوجتك سوف يتم لصقها بالمقالات.
angels
الملائكة
[eerie music]
[موسيقى غريبة]
I'll tell you everything I know
سأخبرك بكل شيء أعرفه
About Angels Club
عن نادي الملائكة
[Meaningful music]
[موسيقى ذات معنى]
the club name
اسم النادي
Are you Angels?
هل أنتم ملائكة؟
[Noisy noise]
[ضوضاء صاخبة]
- [Jehyuk] ‘Apple’ - [Idle] ‘Apple’
- [جيهيوك] "أبل" - [خمول] "أبل"
- [Jehyuk] Once again
- [جيهيوك] مرة أخرى
- [Jehyuk] ‘Angel’ - [Children] ‘Angel’
- [جيهيوك] "ملاك" - [الأطفال] "ملاك"
- What about this? - [Children] ‘Banana’
- ماذا عن هذا؟ - [الأطفال] "الموز"
Very good job
عمل جيد جدا
You did a great job with your homework. Didn't play last week, huh?
لقد قمت بعمل عظيم مع واجباتك المنزلية. لم تلعب الأسبوع الماضي، هاه؟
- [Director] Hello - [Jehyuk’s laughter]
- [المدير] مرحبا - [ضحك جيهيوك]
- Ah - [Director] Team leader
- اه - [المدير] قائد الفريق
Just watch for a moment
مجرد مشاهدة للحظة
[Child] Yes
[الطفل] نعم
[Director] Ah, in the backyard Guests are coming
[المخرج] آه، في الفناء الخلفي الضيوف قادمون
[uneasy music]
[موسيقى مضطربة]
[Grass bug crying]
[بكاء حشرة العشب]
What's going on? Without any contact
ماذا يحدث؟ دون أي اتصال
Then, if anyone catches your eye,
وبعد ذلك، إذا لفت انتباهك أي شخص،
[Jehyuk] This is What are you doing? [Painful groan]
[جيهيوك] هذا هو ماذا تفعل؟ [أنين مؤلم]
[Director] Uh, Chairman.
[المدير] اه، الرئيس.
-What happened without any contact? - [Yujeong’s laughter]
-ماذا حدث دون أي اتصال؟ - [ضحك يوجيونغ]
[Yoojeong] Ah, director, hey, Mr. Jehyuk.
[يوجيونغ] آه، أيها المخرج، مرحبًا السيد جيهيوك.
No, are you above the team leader?
لا، هل أنت فوق قائد الفريق؟
Ah, team leader
آه، قائد الفريق
Where did you go when you had a guest?
أين ذهبت عندما كان لديك ضيف؟
Are you a guest?
هل أنت ضيف؟
[Birdsong]
[أغنية العصافير]
[Yoojeong] Mr. Jehyuk
[يوجيونغ] السيد جيهيوك
Oh no
أوه لا
The face
الوجه
No, why is your face like this?
لا، لماذا وجهك هكذا؟
They said a guest came
قالوا جاء ضيف
Did you have a fight?
هل كان لديك قتال؟
[sigh]
[تنهد]
I called a friend to give me a wedding invitation.
اتصلت بصديق ليعطيني دعوة زفاف.
But
لكن
I don't even know what's inside me
أنا لا أعرف حتى ما بداخلي
I guess there was something like a sense of entitlement.
أعتقد أنه كان هناك شيء مثل الشعور بالاستحقاق.
My friend touched it, so stop...
لقد لمسها صديقي، لذا توقف...
Do you have a sense of entitlement?
هل لديك شعور بالاستحقاق؟
Why Jehyuk?
لماذا جيهيوك؟
They told me to call my boss He said he was good at seducing me.
قالوا لي أن أتصل برئيسي قال إنه كان جيدًا في إغواءي.
This doesn't make sense
هذا لا معنى له
[Yoojeong] How can you say that?
[يوجيونغ] كيف يمكنك أن تقول ذلك؟
- I'm trying to get used to it now. - [Yujeong’s absurd breathing]
- أحاول التعود على ذلك الآن. - [تنفس يوجيونغ السخيف]
They say we live well thanks to women
يقولون أننا نعيش بشكل جيد بفضل النساء
- [Calm music] - This is something you will hear for the rest of your life.
- [موسيقى هادئة] - هذا شيء سوف تسمعه لبقية حياتك.
[disgusted breathing]
[تنفس مقرف]
Leona Jehyuk In the end, it's all the same
ليونا جيهيوك في النهاية، كل شيء هو نفسه
Sticking a straw in a woman's back
لصق القش في ظهر المرأة
[sigh]
[تنهد]
Let's do it like this
دعونا نفعل ذلك مثل هذا
Youngwoon Foundation Chairman
رئيس مؤسسة يونج وون
From now on, I’m Jehyuk.
من الآن فصاعدا، أنا جيهيوك.
[Yoojeong] I created something new Culture and Arts Complex Promotion Committee
[Yoojeong] لقد خلقت شيئًا جديدًا لجنة ترقية مجمع الثقافة والفنون
I will only serve as chairman.
سأعمل فقط كرئيس.
But
لكن
What about the daycare center if I become chairman?
ماذا عن مركز الرعاية النهارية إذا أصبحت رئيسًا؟
[Makes a yuck sound]
[يصدر صوت مقزز]
I'll figure out how to do that
سأكتشف كيفية القيام بذلك
[Yoojeong] So you
[يوجيونغ] إذن أنت
Please serve as Chairman of the Youngwoon Foundation.
يرجى العمل كرئيس لمؤسسة Youngwoon.
[surprised gasp]
[شهقة متفاجئة]
[heavy music]
[موسيقى ثقيلة]
[Haemi] So, only Jay You can't believe it
[هايمي] إذن، جاي فقط لا يمكنك أن تصدق ذلك
You have to find your own way to live
عليك أن تجد طريقتك الخاصة للعيش
[Doorbell sounds]
[أصوات جرس الباب]
[Snort] You too?
[شخير] أنت أيضا؟
[Sound of door closing]
[صوت إغلاق الباب]
[Yuna] Sit down
[يونا] اجلس
[Tense sound effect]
[مؤثرات صوتية متوترة]
[Hae-mi's absurd breathing]
[تنفس هاي مي السخيف]
You are a pumpkin seed I've known it for a long time
أنت بذرة اليقطين لقد عرفت ذلك لفترة طويلة
This is the best ever
هذا هو الأفضل على الإطلاق
[Haemi] How can you tell me Without saying a word
[هايمي] كيف يمكنك أن تخبرني دون أن يقول كلمة واحدة
Come here, come here?
تعال هنا، تعال هنا؟
[Yoojeong] The foundation is in urgent need of money. I couldn't help it
[Yoojeong] المؤسسة في حاجة ماسة إلى المال. لم أستطع مساعدته
[Hae-mi's disapproving breath]
[نفس هاي مي الرافض]
But you came too
لكنك أتيت أيضًا
I predicted it in advance Finding my way to live
لقد توقعت ذلك مقدما العثور على طريقي للعيش
[laughter]
[ضحك]
What old people say That's all right [laughter]
ماذا يقول كبار السن هذا جيد [ضحك]
It's fun to watch the fight
من الممتع مشاهدة القتال
[Haemi laughs]
[يضحك هيمي]
[Yuna] Just say something
[يونا] فقط قل شيئا
When are you going to go?
متى ستذهب؟
Why did you come to me?
لماذا أتيت إلي؟
your land
أرضك
What can I do?
ماذا يمكنني أن أفعل؟
[Haemi] Well, don’t kill people. Don't talk like this
[هايمي] حسنًا، لا تقتل الناس. لا تتحدث بهذه الطريقة
[Sigh] My mouth hurts. repeat what I said
[تنهد] فمي يؤلمني. كرر ما قلته
[Yuna] What I want is That's all there is?
[يونا] ما أريده هو هذا كل ما هناك؟
[Haemi sighs] Well…
[يتنهد هيمي] حسنًا...
It's Yuna
إنها يونا
That's because we really need that land.
وذلك لأننا نحتاج حقًا إلى تلك الأرض.
Please tell me how, okay?
من فضلك قل لي كيف، حسنا؟
[Old] Not only the child’s father Are you saying I need to find my child?
[قديم] ليس والد الطفل فقط هل تقول أنني بحاجة للعثور على طفلي؟
Well, if you go out carelessly, I think it's dangerous
حسنًا، إذا خرجت بلا مبالاة، أعتقد أن هذا خطير
Let alone the kid who attacked you wrongly. I'll have to rot in prison for the rest of my life
ناهيك عن الطفل الذي هاجمك خطأً. سأضطر إلى التعفن في السجن لبقية حياتي
[Yuna] Then let’s do it like this
[يونا] إذن دعونا نفعل ذلك بهذه الطريقة
be friends with me
كن صديقا لي
Like before
مثل قبل
[nervous music]
[موسيقى عصبية]
[Laughing] Didn’t you understand?
[تضحك] ألم تفهمي؟
Be friends with me, like 10 years ago
كن صديقًا لي، كما كان الحال قبل 10 سنوات
[Haemi's embarrassed exclamation]
[تعجب هيمي المحرج]
[absurd laughter]
[ضحكة سخيفة]
You don't know what a friend is, do you?
أنت لا تعرف ما هو الصديق، أليس كذلك؟
[Haemi] My friend is I'm not doing it with just anyone.
[هايمي] صديقي هو أنا لا أفعل ذلك مع أي شخص فقط.
trustworthy Friends are what you do with kids.
جدير بالثقة الأصدقاء هم ما تفعله مع الأطفال.
[absurd laughter]
[ضحكة سخيفة]
[Yuna] You guys came here Isn't it Jay?
[يونا] لقد جئتم إلى هنا يا رفاق أليس كذلك جاي؟
Not knowing the meaning of friends Sounds like you guys?
لا يعرف معنى الأصدقاء يبدو مثلكم يا رفاق؟
- I'm not asking for much. - [Meaningful music]
- أنا لا أطلب الكثير. - [موسيقى ذات معنى]
When you all get together with your husbands
عندما تجتمعون مع أزواجكم
please invite me just once
من فضلك ادعوني مرة واحدة فقط
That way, trust will be built.
وبهذه الطريقة سيتم بناء الثقة.
That way you can make a deal
بهذه الطريقة يمكنك عقد صفقة
Isn't it?
أليس كذلك؟
[Atmospheric music plays]
[تشغيل الموسيقى الجوية]
[Elasticity of oil well]
[مرونة بئر النفط]
[Yujeong’s breathing sound]
[صوت تنفس يوجيونغ]
[Haemi] Hey, are you crazy?
[هيمي] مهلا، هل أنت مجنون؟
Why are you doing something you shouldn't do?
لماذا تفعل شيئًا لا ينبغي عليك فعله؟
[sigh]
[تنهد]
Because I'm scared
لأنني خائفة
Yuna says we should be friends
تقول يونا أننا يجب أن نكون أصدقاء
[Yujeong’s light sigh]
[تنهد يوجيونغ الخفيف]
It's not scary
انها ليست مخيفة
[sigh]
[تنهد]
[Haemi and Yujeong sigh]
[تنهد هيمي ويوجيونج]
[Haemi] Hey, at your wedding Do you want to invite me?
[هيمي] مرحبًا، في حفل زفافك هل تريد دعوتي؟
If it's a gathering where even the husbands come, That's the fastest
إذا كان تجمعًا حيث يأتي حتى الأزواج، هذا هو الأسرع
No, my wedding
لا، حفل زفافي
This marriage has to be perfect
هذا الزواج يجب أن يكون مثاليا
[Haemi] So are you going to give up that land?
[هايمي] إذن هل ستتخلى عن تلك الأرض؟
Then give it to your foundation.
ثم اعطها لمؤسستك.
Donations to our hotel Do I have to retrieve it?
التبرعات لفندقنا هل يجب علي استعادته؟
Hey, that doesn’t work either, suddenly…
مهلا، هذا لا يعمل أيضا، فجأة ...
Where is something like that all of a sudden?
أين يوجد شيء كهذا فجأة؟
This doesn't work, that doesn't work either.
هذا لا يعمل، وهذا لا يعمل أيضا.
[Shouting] Well, what are we going to do?
[صراخ] حسنًا، ماذا سنفعل؟
[Yujeong’s sigh]
[تنهد يوجيونغ]
[Yoojeong] Then
[يوجيونج] إذن
Not a wedding
ليس حفل زفاف
at my house this weekend Shall we all get together once?
في منزلي في نهاية هذا الاسبوع هل سنجتمع جميعا مرة واحدة؟
Our Mr. Jehyuk I became the chairman this time.
السيد جيهيوك أصبحت رئيسا هذه المرة.
Let’s have a celebration party too
دعونا نقيم حفلة احتفال أيضًا
Jehyuk, did you make him chairman?
جيهيوك، هل جعلته رئيسًا؟
[light sigh]
[تنهد خفيف]
But
لكن
What should I say to Jay?
ماذا يجب أن أقول لجاي؟
[Yoojeong] You invited Yuna Shouldn't I say it?
[Yoojeong] لقد قمت بدعوة يونا ألا يجب أن أقول ذلك؟
Don't say it first
لا تقل ذلك أولاً
[Haemi] Then we can secretly today I also visited Yuna
[هايمي] إذن يمكننا سرا اليوم لقد زرت يونا أيضًا
You have to blow
عليك أن تهب
When I see you at your house later Let's solve it then
عندما أراك في منزلك لاحقا دعونا حلها بعد ذلك
[Yujeong’s light sigh]
[تنهد يوجيونغ الخفيف]
[Haemi’s swallowing sound]
[صوت ابتلاع هيمي]
[Jay] This is February 18th All event venues in Gunggok District
[جاي] هذا هو 18 فبراير جميع أماكن الفعاليات في منطقة Gunggok
You mean it's a reservation situation?
هل تقصد أنها حالة حجز؟
[Yongpil] However, in the data provided,
[يونغبيل] ومع ذلك، في البيانات المقدمة،
It's called Angel's Club.
إنه يسمى نادي الملائكة
Something like a secret club opening ceremony There was no
شيء مثل حفل افتتاح النادي السري لم يكن هناك
[Sighing] Kim Man-bok It definitely did.
[تنهد] كيم مان بوك لقد فعلت ذلك بالتأكيد.
It opens in exactly one week
سيتم افتتاحه خلال أسبوع واحد بالضبط
Then you can't do it
ثم لا يمكنك أن تفعل ذلك
[Yongpil] On this day in the Gunggok district At events held
[يونغبيل] في مثل هذا اليوم في منطقة جونجوك في المناسبات التي أقيمت
I have no choice but to send everyone out.
ليس لدي خيار سوى إرسال الجميع للخارج.
good
جيد
Are you watching well?
هل تراقب جيدا؟
[Yongpil] Ever since I met Ki Yun-cheol There was no special activity
[يونغبيل] منذ أن التقيت كي يون تشيول لم يكن هناك أي نشاط خاص
It's about a business I used to do business with.
يتعلق الأمر بعمل كنت أتعامل معه.
- [Meaningful music] - I went to an unexpected place once.
- [موسيقى ذات معنى] - ذهبت إلى مكان غير متوقع مرة واحدة.
[cell phone vibrates]
[يهتز الهاتف الخليوي]
[Haemi] Go Yoo-na
[هيمي] اذهب يو نا
Yujeong is coming home this Saturday
Yujeong يعود إلى المنزل هذا السبت
I'll send you the address and time again.
سأرسل لك العنوان والوقت مرة أخرى.
[sigh]
[تنهد]
Are we finally seeing it?
هل نراها أخيراً؟
[Yuna] Tell me
[يونا] أخبريني
my ex husband
زوجي السابق
Who's the big guy looking after you?
من هو الرجل الكبير الذي يعتني بك؟
[Sound of intake of breath]
[صوت أخذ نفس]
National Intelligence Service?
جهاز المخابرات الوطني؟
no
لا
[President Jeong] FBI because you’re from the United States?
[الرئيس جيونغ] مكتب التحقيقات الفيدرالي لأنك من الولايات المتحدة؟
[Yelling] President Jeong!
[صراخ] الرئيس جيونج!
[President Jeong] Oh, it’s true
[الرئيس جيونغ] أوه، هذا صحيح
That much is shrouded in mystery?
إلى هذا الحد يكتنفه الغموض؟
With the skills I used to dig up after the big guys, I tried to shake it all off.
بالمهارات التي استخدمتها للبحث عن الكبار، حاولت التخلص من كل شيء.
[Clicking tongue] I didn’t know.
[نقر اللسان] لم أكن أعرف.
[telephone ringing sound]
[صوت رنين الهاتف]
[nervous music]
[موسيقى عصبية]
[Continued phone ringing]
[استمرار رنين الهاتف]
yes
نعم
In front of the hotel?
أمام الفندق؟
Who?
من؟
[Yuna] If you came this far Without coming up?
[يونا] إذا وصلت إلى هذا الحد دون أن يأتي؟
scared?
مقدس؟
Reminds me of the old days?
يذكرني بالأيام الخوالي؟
[Heavy sound effect]
[مؤثرات صوتية ثقيلة]
I want to drive with you
أريد أن أقود معك
Where do you want to go with me?
أين تريد أن تذهب معي؟
You'll find out when you go
ستكتشف ذلك عندما تذهب
[Music that heightens tension]
[الموسيقى التي تزيد من التوتر]
[Car engine sound]
[صوت محرك السيارة]
[Sound of children talking]
[صوت أطفال يتحدثون]
[Car start sound stops]
[يتوقف صوت تشغيل السيارة]
[Sound of seatbelt being unfastened]
[صوت فك حزام الأمان]
[sigh]
[تنهد]
[Jay] Well, it didn’t come out today.
[جاي] حسنًا، لم يصدر اليوم.
- I'll have to look for it. - [Sound of car door opening]
- سآخذ للبحث عنه. - [صوت فتح باب السيارة]
[Yuna’s dumbfounded laughter]
[ضحكة يونا المذهولة]
[Sound of children talking]
[صوت أطفال يتحدثون]
[Sound of seatbelt being unfastened]
[صوت فك حزام الأمان]
[Sound of car door closing]
[صوت إغلاق باب السيارة]
[Yuna] What are you?
[يونا] ماذا أنت؟
Why did you bring me here?
لماذا أحضرتني إلى هنا؟
[Jay] To find your daughter
[جاي] للعثور على ابنتك
you
أنت
Did you put someone behind me?
هل وضعت شخص ما خلفي؟
[absurd snort]
[شخير سخيف]
Actually
في الواقع
you are righteous You weren't a lawyer
أنت صالح أنت لم تكن محاميا
[Yuna] A guy like Jeong Gu-tae If you look at what was done,
[يونا] رجل مثل جيونج جو تاي فإذا نظرت إلى ما تم فعله،
So?
إذن؟
How much did you find out?
كم اكتشفت؟
About me
عني
[Meaningful music]
[موسيقى ذات معنى]
On your parole
على الإفراج المشروط الخاص بك
You cannot go abroad without permission. There is a condition
لا يمكنك السفر إلى الخارج دون إذن. هناك شرط
[Jay] But you broke it You went to America, right?
[جاي] لكنك كسرته لقد ذهبت إلى أمريكا، أليس كذلك؟
That is
هذا هو
You're a wanted man in Korea
أنت رجل مطلوب في كوريا
As you are Emily Go It's a shame that I came
كما كنت إميلي الذهاب ومن العار أن جئت
Otherwise you would have been arrested. at the airport
وإلا لكان قد تم القبض عليك. في المطار
[laughter]
[ضحك]
It's nothing special
لا شيء خاص
[Yuna] I again They found out my ex-husband
[يونا] أنا مرة أخرى اكتشفوا زوجي السابق
Are you not scared of me?
هل أنت لست خائفا مني؟
[Jay] Just one phone call from me
[جاي] مكالمة هاتفية واحدة فقط مني
you are under arrest right now
أنت رهن الاعتقال الآن
- [Yuna] If you’re scared of prison, etc. - [Nervous music]
- [يونا] إذا كنت خائفة من السجن، وما إلى ذلك. - [موسيقى عصبية]
You probably didn't even think about coming
ربما لم تفكر حتى في المجيء
I came prepared to die, I
لقد جئت مستعدًا للموت، أنا
[Jay] Let’s make a deal
[جاي] دعونا نعقد صفقة
Give me your land
أعطني أرضك
Then no matter what method I use
ثم بغض النظر عن الطريقة التي أستخدمها
I'll get your daughter from your ex-husband.
سأحصل على ابنتك من زوجك السابق.
What do you think?
ماذا تعتقد؟
Trust me once
صدقني مرة واحدة
null
null
Believe it?
صدق ذلك؟
[Tense sound effect]
[مؤثرات صوتية متوترة]
If [sigh]
إذا [تنهد]
What if my child’s father is Mr. Kang-hoo?
ماذا لو كان والد طفلي هو السيد كانغ هو؟
- [Nervous music] - Can you still fight?
- [موسيقى عصبية] - هل لا يزال بإمكانك القتال؟
for me
بالنسبة لي
What nonsense...
ما هذا الهراء ...
When did you guys break up?
متى انفصلتم يا رفاق؟
me
أنا
I met Kang Hoo before going to the US.
التقيت كانغ هوو قبل الذهاب إلى الولايات المتحدة.
[Yuna] We were pretty hot
[يونا] كنا ساخنين جدًا
I guess Mr. Kang-hoo didn’t tell you?
أعتقد أن السيد كانغ هو لم يخبرك؟
Jay
جاي
What I mean is
ما أعنيه هو
What to believe in the world There is nothing
ما يجب أن نؤمن به في العالم لا يوجد شيء
So don't trust anyone
لذلك لا تثق بأحد
Even Yujeong and Haemi
حتى يوجيونغ وهايمي
[creaking sound]
[صوت صرير]
Who is my child's father? You'll find out soon enough
من هو والد طفلي؟ سوف تكتشف قريبا بما فيه الكفاية
If you still want to help me then
إذا كنت لا تزال تريد مساعدتي ثم
do that
افعل ذلك
Then I will give you my land
ثم سأعطيك أرضي
I guess the desire to give me a ride has disappeared.
أعتقد أن الرغبة في اصطحابي قد اختفت.
I'll go alone
سأذهب وحدي
[Sound of Yuna’s footsteps moving away]
[صوت خطى يونا تبتعد]
[Music that heightens the mood]
[موسيقى تحسن المزاج]
[Sound of plates rattling]
[صوت خشخشة الأطباق]
[Kanghu] I’ll wait
[كانغو] سأنتظر
let me do it
اسمحوا لي أن أفعل ذلك
Well, he put it aside to give it to me.
حسنًا، لقد وضعه جانبًا ليعطيه لي.
[light laughter]
[ضحكة خفيفة]
What's going on today?
ماذا يحدث اليوم؟
Don’t eat ramen and soju?
لا تأكل رامين وسوجو؟
Today
اليوم
- [Meaningful music] - Just, kinda.
- [موسيقى ذات معنى] - فقط نوعاً ما.
Because I don’t want to mess around
لأنني لا أريد العبث
[rattling sound]
[صوت قعقعة]
[Sound of Ganghu taking a deep breath]
[صوت جانجو وهو يأخذ نفسًا عميقًا]
[Sound of cutting a knife]
[صوت قطع سكين]
[Soaring music]
[موسيقى صاخبة]
Hey there
مرحبًا
[Jay] Yuna
[جاي] يونا
Have you ever met since you were released from prison?
هل التقيتما منذ خروجكما من السجن؟
[Kanghu] No, there is none.
[كانغو] لا، لا يوجد شيء.
Then
ثم
When was the last time you saw it?
متى كانت آخر مرة رأيتها؟
[Ganghu’s chomping sound]
[صوت قضم بصوت عالي جانجو]
[Kanghu] I’m the same as you
[كانغو] أنا مثلك
Before that incident happened
قبل وقوع تلك الحادثة
Today is a little strange
اليوم غريب بعض الشيء
What happened?
ماذا حدث؟
no
لا
It's nothing
لا شيء
I'll go and see
سأذهب وأرى
I'll take you there
سآخذك إلى هناك
[Sound of chair being dragged]
[صوت الكرسي الذي يتم سحبه]
No, don't come out.
لا، لا تخرج.
[Jay] I’ll go
[جاي] سأذهب
[Sound of Jay’s footsteps moving away]
[صوت خطى جاي وهي تبتعد]
[Call connection tone]
[نغمة اتصال المكالمة]
Manager
مدير
Go Yoo-na's daughter
اذهب ابنة يو نا
Please find out who my dad is
يرجى معرفة من هو والدي
[Call end sound]
[صوت نهاية المكالمة]
[cell phone closing sound]
[صوت إغلاق الهاتف الخليوي]
[Oven notification sound]
[صوت إشعار الفرن]
[Jehyuk’s expectant breathing]
[تنفس جيهيوك المتوقع]
[Sound of approaching footsteps]
[صوت خطوات تقترب]
[Yoojeong] Oh, it smells so good
[يوجيونغ] أوه، رائحتها طيبة جدًا
[breath mixed with laughter]
[نفس ممزوج بالضحك]
[Yujeong and Jehyuk’s light smile]
[ابتسامة يوجيونغ وجيهيوك الخفيفة]
When you get married, the kitchen I think Jehyuk will take over.
عندما تتزوجين المطبخ أعتقد أن جيهيوك سيتولى المسؤولية.
[Jehyuk and Yujeong’s light smile]
[ابتسامة جيهيوك ويوجيونغ الخفيفة]
[Yoojeong] What the hell is Mr. Jehyuk? What can’t you do?
[يوجيونغ] ما هو السيد جيهيوك بحق الجحيم؟ ما الذي لا يمكنك فعله؟
Making money?
كسب المال؟
- [Jehyuk and Yujeong’s laughter] - [Calm music]
- [ضحكة جيهيوك ويوجيونغ] - [موسيقى هادئة]
[Jehyuk] At home They told me not to wear corrective shoes
[جيهيوك] في المنزل قالوا لي ألا أرتدي أحذية تصحيحية
I need to rest my feet too.
أحتاج إلى راحة قدمي أيضًا.
Even if you get married, stay at home I'll always be wearing this
حتى لو تزوجت إبقى في البيت سأرتدي هذا دائمًا
Just a perfect look for Jehyuk. I want to be seen
مجرد نظرة مثالية لجيهيوك. أريد أن أرى
[Sound of tapping feet]
[صوت نقر الأقدام]
It's perfect just like this
انها مثالية تماما مثل هذا
To me
لي
[light laughter]
[ضحكة خفيفة]
Mr. Jehyuk
السيد جيهيوك
I'm going to tell you everything today
سأخبرك بكل شيء اليوم
No way
لا مفر
That's after getting married We decided to talk slowly.
وذلك بعد الزواج قررنا التحدث ببطء.
no
لا
Jehyuk is my leg As if I don't think of it as a flaw
جيهيوك رجلي كما لو أنني لا أعتقد أنه عيب
I also meet Jehyuk’s condition. I don't think it's a flaw
أنا أيضًا أتوافق مع حالة جيهيوك. لا أعتقد أنه عيب
[Yoojeong] Rather, sooner rather than later I want to show off
[Yoojeong] بل عاجلاً وليس آجلاً أريد التباهي
To my friends
الى اصدقائي
[light laughter]
[ضحكة خفيفة]
[Yujeong and Jehyuk’s light smile]
[ابتسامة يوجيونغ وجيهيوك الخفيفة]
[Elegant music plays]
[تشغيل الموسيقى الأنيقة]
[Leo’s exclamation]
[تعجب الأسد]
[Leo] This Did you prepare everything?
[ليو] هذا هل أعددت كل شيء؟
[Haemi] I have to do this at least Thanks to someone, I became the chairman of the board.
[هايمي] لا بد لي من القيام بذلك على الأقل بفضل شخص ما، أصبحت رئيس مجلس الإدارة.
[Jehyuk’s embarrassed breathing]
[تنفس جيهيوك المحرج]
What about Kang-hoo?
ماذا عن كانغ هوو؟
[Jay] Oh, well, even on weekends Because I run a restaurant
[جاي] أوه، حسنًا، حتى في عطلات نهاية الأسبوع لأنني أدير مطعماً
- [Jay] He probably won’t come. - [Haemi] Oh, that’s a relief.
- [جاي] ربما لن يأتي. - [هيمي] أوه، هذا مريح.
Ah, Kang-hoo, you must be tired. I need to rest
آه، كانغ هو، لا بد أنك متعب. انا بحاجة للراحة
[Haemi’s awkward laughter]
[ضحكة هيمي المحرجة]
[Leo] Now, now, now, this Put it in front of food and drag it for a long time
[ليو] الآن، الآن، الآن، هذا ضعيه أمام الطعام واسحبيه لفترة طويلة
That's torture, let's start now.
هذا تعذيب، فلنبدأ الآن.
- [Rattling sound] - No
- [صوت قعقعة] - لا
There is someone who hasn't arrived yet
هناك من لم يصل بعد
- Who? - [Nervous music]
- من؟ - [موسيقى عصبية]
[Awkward laughter]
[ضحكة محرجة]
You'll find out when you come
ستكتشف ذلك عندما تأتي
Take care of it in advance Don't lose your appetite
اعتني بها مقدما لا تفقد شهيتك
Ah
اه
before guests arrive
قبل وصول الضيوف
Only in front of my close friends I have something to say
فقط أمام أصدقائي المقربين لدي شيء لأقوله
[Yoojeong] Me
[يوجيونغ] أنا
I'll have a beautiful daughter soon
سيكون لدي ابنة جميلة قريبا
[Haemi’s surprised gasp]
[شهقة هيمي المفاجئة]
- [Leo’s throat coughs and an embarrassed exclamation] - [Haemi’s surprised gasp]
- [يسعل ليو في الحلق ويصرخ محرجًا] - [شهقة هيمي المفاجئة]
Hon, premarital pregnancy?
عزيزتي، الحمل قبل الزواج؟
[Haemi] Hey
[هيمي] مهلا
These pumpkin seeds, really.
بذور اليقطين هذه، حقاً.
That's not it
هذا ليس كل شيء
Actually
في الواقع
- [Mobile phone vibrating sound] - Our Jehyuk
- [صوت اهتزاز الهاتف المحمول] - جيهيوك لدينا
-Before you met me... - [Jay] Yes, manager.
-قبل أن تقابلني.. - [جاي] نعم، أيها المدير.
[Yongpil] I’m with my friends now Are you together?
[يونغبيل] أنا مع أصدقائي الآن هل أنتم معا؟
Yes, what about it?
نعم ماذا عنها؟
Let’s go outside for a moment and talk on the phone.
دعنا نخرج للحظة ونتحدث على الهاتف.
Ah, yes
اه نعم
[Jay] Wait a minute I'll go out and make a phone call.
[جاي] انتظر لحظة سأخرج وأجري مكالمة هاتفية.
[Yoojeong] Oh
[يوجيونغ] أوه
[Haemi] Ah, at an important moment
[هايمي] آه، في لحظة مهمة
[Jay] I’m out, manager.
[جاي] أنا خارج، أيها المدير.
Please speak
من فضلك تحدث
Go Yoo-na's child's father
جو والد طفل يو نا
Who are you?
من أنت؟
[Haemi] Oh, why doesn’t he come here?
[هايمي] أوه، لماذا لا يأتي إلى هنا؟
Ah, hey, until I come back I can't wait
آه، مهلا، حتى أعود لا استطيع الانتظار
Talk to me quickly
تحدث معي بسرعة
Unless you are pregnant before marriage
إلا إذا كنت حاملاً قبل الزواج
That you will have a daughter What on earth are you talking about?
أنه سيكون لديك ابنة ما الذي تتحدث عنه بحق السماء؟
[Yoojeong] To Jehyuk I have a daughter
[يوجيونغ] إلى جيهيوك لدي ابنة
[Soaring music]
[موسيقى صاخبة]
My daughter's name is Nana
اسم ابنتي نانا
I'm 4 years old now
عمري 4 سنوات الآن
[Yuna] Do you understand now?
[يونا] هل فهمت الآن؟
[Sound of shoes again and again]
[صوت الأحذية مرارا وتكرارا]
That's right
هذا صحيح
That guy is the father of my child
هذا الرجل هو والد طفلي
[Heavy sound effect]
[مؤثرات صوتية ثقيلة]
[dark music]
[الموسيقى المظلمة]
[Yujeong’s trembling breathing]
[تنفس يوجيونج المرتعش]
[Yujeong’s heavy breathing]
[تنفس يوجيونغ الثقيل]
[Cell phone operation sound]
[صوت تشغيل الهاتف الخليوي]
[Call connection tone]
[نغمة اتصال المكالمة]
[secret music]
[الموسيقى السرية]
[Yuna] I warned you, right?
[يونا] لقد حذرتك، أليس كذلك؟
Don't trust anyone
لا تثق بأحد
The couple gets along well There is only one way to live well
الزوجان يتعايشان بشكل جيد هناك طريقة واحدة فقط للعيش بشكل جيد
Never letting each other know our secrets Isn’t that right, Haemi?
لا نسمح لبعضنا البعض أبدًا بمعرفة أسرارنا أليس هذا صحيحاً يا هيمي؟
[Haemi] But why did you do that yesterday?
[هايمي] لكن لماذا فعلت ذلك بالأمس؟
Like a rabbit caught in a wolf's den I'm so scared
مثل أرنب وقع في وكر الذئب أنا خائف جدا
[Yuna] Isn’t that the case?
[يونا] أليس هذا هو الحال؟
Before marriage My husband, who I thought was an angel
قبل الزواج زوجي الذي كنت أظنه ملاكاً
It turns out he was the devil
اتضح أنه كان الشيطان
Very 'surprise', surprisingly
"مفاجأة" جدًا، بشكل مدهش
[Kanghu] Trust me
[كانغو] ثق بي
No matter what anyone says
بغض النظر عما يقوله أي شخص
[Yoojeong] I’m Jehyuk
[Yoojeong] أنا جيهيوك
My mom and dad in the sky It's like a gift you sent me
أمي وأبي في السماء إنها مثل الهدية التي أرسلتها لي
[Yuna] So
[يونا] إذن
Whose side will you be on?
إلى أي جانب ستقف؟
Song Jehyuk?
أغنية جيهيوك؟
Or me?
أو أنا؟
[Jai] Good people, bad people It's all relative
[جاي] أناس طيبون، أناس سيئون كل شيء نسبي
Tang, Go Yoo-na, I will solve everything.
تانغ، اذهب يو نا، سأحل كل شيء.
- Niga - [Grunting sound]
- نيغا - [صوت الشخير]
No matter how much I pretend to be Emily Go, you are unique
بغض النظر عن مدى تظاهري بأنني إميلي جو، أنت فريد
[Yuna's heavy breathing] Dojae!
{\an8[نفس يونا الثقيل] دوجاي!